翻译：隐藏的Sebb  校对：克里斯鸡毛
大家好啊 我是鲍比·莱伯
Hey, everyone, it's Bobby Leiber
欢迎收听你们最喜欢的播客
and welcome to your favorite podcast
石墙的第十一块砖头
The 11th Brick at Stonewall.
因为我们都知道 在石墙事件中
Because we all know a butch lesbian
也许扔出第一块砖头的
or a trans woman of color
是一位男性化女同 或是一位有色变性女人
probably threw the first brick at Stonewall
但扔出第十一块砖头的是一位顺性的白人男同
but it was a cis, white, gay man who threw the 11th brick.
今天 如同往常 我将带你踏上一段旅程
And today, as always, I will take you on a journey
贯穿LGBTQ+的历史 更重要的是
throughout LGBTQ+ history and, much more importantly
讲一些关于我自己的 以及我想聊什么就聊什么
my own problems and whatever I feel like talking about.
今天也是一个很重要的日子 因为今天
And this is a big day, because, as of today
我们要庆祝石墙的第十一块砖头达到一百万订阅
The 11th Brick is celebrating one million subscribers.
为了纪念这一激动人心的消息
And in honor of all this exciting news
我将现场回答你们的问题
I am taking your questions live.
第一个问题  嗨 鲍比
First question.  Hi, Bobby.
有机会出版更多的儿童书籍吗？
Any chance for more children's books?
噢 目前没有 但谢谢你
Oh, not at the moment, but thank you.
正如你们中的一些人所知 我写了一系列的儿童书籍
As some of you know, I wrote a series of children's books
以帮助父母教育孩子了解同性恋历史
to help parents teach kids about gay history
但并没有人去买
which no one bought.
事实证明 一个四岁的孩子并不想听
Turns out a four year old didn't want to hear
关于玛蒂娜 纳芙拉蒂洛娃的睡前故事
a bedtime story about Martina Navratilova.
嘿 父母们 谢谢你们教孩子们了解
Hey, parents, thanks for teaching your kids about
圣诞老人 一位不存在的直男
Santa Claus, a straight man that doesn't exist
而不是玛蒂娜 纳芙拉蒂诺娃 一位存在的女同性恋者
and not Martina Navratilova, a lesbian who does.
另一则消息 我终于拿到了我的试镜录像
In other news, I finally got the footage from my audition
成为 "粉熊救兵 "的下一位卡司
to be part of the next cast of Queer Eye
你现在就可以在手机APP上观看
and you can watch that on the app right now.
噢 不  噢 我的...
Oh, no.  Oh, my...
不好意思 这没什么好哭的
I'm sorry. This is not sad.
根本不需要哭吧
It's just not sad.
你们也就给他理了个发 穿了条裤子
You gave him a haircut and a pair of pants.
我是说 他看起来一般
I mean, he looks fine.
并没有很好  下一位来电
Not great.  Next caller.
你写的那部电影怎么了？
What ever happened to that movie you wrote?
噢 对了 那部电影
Oh, yeah. The movie.
这些大电影制片人找上我 说：
These big movie producers came to me and said
"我们想让你写一部关于同性恋的爱情喜剧
"We want you to write a rom com about a gay couple.
"一部全世界都会喜欢的
"Something the whole world would enjoy.
"甚至直男也可能会喜欢的
"Something that a straight guy might even like
并且会和他的女朋友一起看 " 我说
and watch with his girlfriend." I said
"一部直男可能也会喜欢的？到底是一部怎么样的？
"Something a straight guy might like? Like what exactly?
"我是不是要在疯狂热恋的同时
"Am I gonna be in the middle of some high speed chase
"然后突然爱上艾斯·库伯？
"and then all of a sudden fall in love with Ice Cube?
"我是不是要为杰森·莫玛做0？
"Am I gonna get butt fucked by Jason Momoa
与此同时 怎么说呢 去担心火山喷发的问题？"
while we're both, I don't know, worrying about a volcano?"
他说 "鲍比 我们只是想拍一部电影
And he said, "Bobby, we just want to make a movie
"让世界看到同性恋和异性恋的关系
"that shows the world gay and straight relationships
"都是一样的
"are the same.
爱就是爱就是爱"
Love is love is love."
我说 "爱就是爱就是爱？
I said, "Love is love is love?
"不 不是的 那是胡说八道
"No, it's not. That's bullshit.
"那是我们不得不编造的谎言 以说服你们这些白痴
"That is a lie we had to make up to convince you idiots
"最终公平地对待我们
"to finally treat us fairly.
"爱不是爱
"Love is not love.
"我们的关系是不同的
"Our relationships are different.
我们的性生活是不同的 "
Our sex lives are different."
他说 "鲍比 我们只是想拍一部
And he said, "Bobby, we were just trying to make
关于好同志的好电影"
a nice movie about nice gay people."
我说 "好吧 那你就错了
And I said, "Well, there's your first mistake
因为不是所有的同志都是好人 "
because not all gay people are nice."
然后我就起身离开了
And I got up and left.
总之 不拍也没事
Anyway, it's totally fine.
反正我不是写爱情喜剧的合适人选
I'm not the right person to write a rom com anyway.
为什么不呢？
Why not?
呃 我不知道
Um, I don't know.
我的意思是 我已经40岁了 我从来没有谈过恋爱
I mean, I'm 40 years old. I've never been in love.
我甚至没有过一段严肃的关系 这倒没什么
I've never even had a serious relationship, which is fine.
我爱我的生活 我爱自由的我
You know, I love my life. I love my freedom.
我爱独立的我 但是 你懂吧
I love my independence, but, you know
也许这就意味着我不是写爱情故事的
probably means I'm not the right person
合适人选
to write a love story.
激动人心的消息是 我仍然非常饥渴
In exciting news, I remain very horny
并且今晚我很荣幸能够参加 LGBTQ+骄傲颁奖典礼
and tonight I am being honored at the LGBTQ+ Pride Awards.
作为国家橄榄球联盟的一员 我从未想过我可以出柜
Being in the NFL, I never thought I could come out.
多年来 我不得不承受着作为一个身材火辣 魁梧的同志
For years, I had to suffer as a hot, ripped, gay person
过着不为人知的生活
living my life in private.
但过去的一年 真的让我明白了
But this last year has really shown me
当你最终作为火辣的同志公开时 生活会变得多么奇妙
how amazing life can be when you are finally publicly hot.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
现在 请欢迎
And now, please welcome
艾美奖和托尼奖得主克里斯丁·昌姆沃斯
Emmy and Tony Award winner Kristin Chenoweth.
晚上好
Good evening.
今晚我很荣幸来到这里
What an honor for me to be here tonight.
我头上戴着一顶描绘石墙暴动事件的帽子
On my head is a hat depicting the Stonewall riots
同性恋者解放运动从这里开始
where the queer liberation movement began.
现在 颁发年度最佳顺性白人男同的奖项
And now, the award for cis, white, gay man of the year.
请欢迎 鲍比·莱伯
Please welcome Bobby Leiber.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
噢 我的天哪
Oh, my goodness.
谢谢你 纽约！谢谢你们！
Thank you, New York! Thank you!
谢谢你们
Thank you.
认识一下 克努姆霍特普和尼安克努姆
Meet Khnumhotep and Niankhkhnum
古埃及的伯特和厄尼
the Bert and Ernie of Ancient Egypt.
许多学者认为 他们是
Many scholars believe that they are
历史上第一对有记录的同性伴侣
the first recorded same sex couple in history.
然而 时至今日 仍有历史学家
Yet to this day, there are historians
拒绝相信他们俩是恋人
who refuse to believe that these men were lovers
并坚称他们是兄弟关系
and insist that they were brothers instead.
因此 五千年前就开始的同性恋爱情故事
Thus began 5,000 years of queer love stories
从历史书中抹去
erased from the history books.
没有同性恋的爱情故事来教导我们关于爱
No gay love stories to teach us about love
以及如何去爱对方
and how to love each other.
好吧 今天 我可以高兴地说 这种抹杀结束了
Well, I'm happy to say this erasure ends today.
我非常激动地向你们宣布我接受了一个职位
And I am thrilled to announce I have accepted a position
作为第一个国家LGBTQ+历史博物馆的
as the executive director of the first
执行董事
national LGBTQ+ history museum
就在纽约市!
right here in New York City!
谢谢你 纽约!
Thank you, New York!
谢谢你们
Thank you.
非常感谢你们
Thank you so much.
嘿 怎么样？
Hey, what's up?
约吗？喜好？
Looking? Into?
我是0
Bottom here.
0.5
Versatile.
你当然是
Sure you are.
嘿 怎么样？ 嘿 怎么样？
Hey, what's up?  Hey, what's up?
谢谢你
Thank you.
你想完成吗？
You want to finish?
呃 我想我很好 其实
Uh, I think I'm good, actually.
好的 我给你拿点东西来擦擦  好的
Okay, I'll get you something for that.  Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
很显然
♪ It's very clear ♪
我们的爱在这里停留...
♪ Our love is here to stay... ♪
通常在经历了一段冷淡而又尴尬的
For me, the cold and awkward
Grindr勾搭之后
Grindr hookup is often followed by
我都会独自在城市里散步
a walk around the city by myself.
有跟我一样喜欢这样做的吗？
Anyone else do that?
挺奇怪的 毕竟你还是有过
It's weird, because you still had
这一段浪漫的邂逅
like, this romantic encounter.
即使比较奇怪 或是不太满意
Even though it was odd or unsatisfying
你甚至不认识那个人
and you don't even know the person
你仍然会感觉到这种
you're still feeling this kind of
性爱后的温暖和憧憬
post sex warmth and wistfulness.
所以 我通常会去散步一会
So I usually walk around for a bit
只要这种温暖的感觉还在
and I kind of coast on that warm feeling
我都会回味一番
as long as it lasts.
在 与你不喜欢的陌生人进行奇怪的性行为
And between the weird sex with strangers that you don't like
以及 与你永远不会发生性关系的
and conversations with friends you love
好朋友的谈笑风生 之间
that you would never have sex with, you know
你会拼凑出一版浪漫的单身生活
you cobble together a version of a romantic single life.
这还挺好的 你知道吗？
And it's good, you know?
是能行得通的
It works.
这比
It's a lot more than
这个世界上 很多其他人所拥有的还要多
what a lot of other people have in this world.
你要试着记住这一点
And you try to remember that.
走了很长很长的路......
♪ Going a long, long way... ♪
一如既往 该播客是
As always, this podcast is
由 "事业驴 "为您带来
brought to you by Career Donkey.
嗨 嗨 我很抱歉
Hi, hi. I'm sorry.
我知道 我很抱歉
I I know. I'm sorry.
好吧 发生了什么事？我错过了什么？
All right, what's going on? What did I miss?
你们好吗 卢卡斯？
How are you guys, Lucas?
呃 是这样的 我们的代孕妈妈
Uh, well, our surrogate
怀孕刚满三个月 而且 不仅如此 我们是要...
just hit three months, and, not only that, but we are...
有三胞胎了！ 三胞...
Having triplets!  Trip...
噢 我的天 恭喜你！ 这太不可思议了 是啊！
Oh, my God, congratulations!  That's amazing. Yeah!
我很抱歉 大伙们 我得走了
I'm sorry, you guys. I have to go.
要去酒吧上晚班
A late shift at the bar.
但很高兴见到你们
But it was great meeting you guys.
很高兴见到你 祝贺你们
Nice to meet you.  And congratulations, boys.
谢谢你  再见 马蒂
Thank you.  Bye, Marty.
回头见 给我们发短信  再见
See you later. Text us.  Bye, y'all.
等等 发生什么了？
Wait, so what's happening?
你们不是结婚了吗
Didn't you guys have an announcement?
好吧 呃  我完全知道这有点奇怪
Okay, uh, so, I totally know this is a little weird
而且有点出乎意料 但我们之所以
and unexpected, but the reason we've been
和马蒂在一起玩这么久 是因为
hanging around with Marty so much is that
我们正在和他约会
we are kind of dating him.
噢  好吧
Oh.  Okay.
等一下
Wait a second.
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
你说你们在和他约会是什么意思？
What do you mean you're dating him?
我的意思是 在一起 就像夫夫一样
I mean, together, like, as a couple.
我们在和他约会
We're seeing him.
我想这有点像组成三人家庭的情况
I guess it's kind of like a throuple situation.
等一下
Hold on.
等等 那到底是什么意思？
So, wait, what does that mean exactly?
你是说 你们只是在玩3P还是什么？
Like, are you guys just having threesomes or something?
好吧 我们勾搭上了 但后来我们开始
Well, we hooked up, but then we started spending
花了很多时间在一起
a bunch of time together after.
结果发现 我们有很多共同点
It turns out we have a lot in common.
不仅仅是关于性爱 我们是真心喜欢对方的
It's more than just sex. We genuinely like each other.
等等 等等 那么 这已经持续多久了？
Wait, wait. So, how long has this been going on?
六个月？ 噢
Six months?  Oh.
六个月... 你们三口之家已经六个月了
Six mon  You're in a throuple for six months
而你却没有告诉我？
and you didn't tell me?
我们也不知道会变得那么认真
We didn't know it'd get that serious.
能有多认真？你们是三口之家
How serious is it gonna get? You're in a throuple.
接下来要做什么 告诉你的爷爷奶奶？
What are you gonna do next, tell your grandparents?
嗨 奶奶
Hi, Grandma.
哦 嗨 亲爱的
Oh, hi, honey.
我想告诉你一些事情  怎么了？
I have some news.  Yes?
彼得和我 我们一起和第三个人做爱了！
Peter and I are jointly fucking a third person!
噢 我的天哪！
Oh, my goodness!
保罗打来的
It's Paul.
他和彼得 和第三个人做爱了！
He and Peter are jointly fucking someone else!
噢 多好啊 三口之家
Oh, how wonderful. It's a throuple.
噢
Oh.
我们会没事的
We'll be fine.
我们真的是非常信任对方才这样的
We really trust each other enough to do this.
你们还是谨慎一点吧
Just be careful.
我认识有很多做过这样事情的人
I know a lot of guys who've done this
通常都是滑坡效应
and it's a slippery slope.
感情是脆弱的 而且 你也知道 我们是男人
These things are fragile, and, you know, we're men.
知道吗？男人和男人约会 爱根本就不是爱
Okay? Men dating men. Love is not love.
男人都是好色的、自私的、愚蠢的 我也一样
We are horny and selfish and stupid. I am, too.
记得有一天 有人打电话到我的节目 问我
Yeah, someone called into my show the other day and asked me
为什么我仍然是单身 我说 "你想知道为什么吗？
why I'm still single. I said, "You want to know why?
"因为我一辈子都是男同
"Because I've been gay my whole life
而且 我不相信这些该死的男同 "
and I don't trust these gay motherfuckers."
我支持他们 但我不信任他们
I support them, but I don't trust them.
那你过得开心吗？ 谁会一直这么开心？
And are you happy?  Who's so happy all the time?
呃 很多人
Uh, a lot of people.
呃 我真的不相信那些人
Well, I really don't trust those people.
莱伯先生？
Mr. Leiber?
很抱歉打扰你 我喜欢你的播客
Sorry. I love your podcast.
我可以 我可以来张自拍吗？ 噢 当然可以
Can I, can I get a selfie?  Oh, sure.
谢谢你
Thank you.
惨了
Mm hmm.  Shit.
我和亨利约好了要在发布会上和他见面
I told Henry I'd meet him at this launch party.
害 我想先回家换衣服
Ugh, I wanted to go home and change first.
反正你们男同不都要脱掉你们的上衣吗
Aren't you guys just gonna take your shirts off anyway?
你错了 我们不只是要脱掉我们的上衣
No, we're not just gonna take our shirts off.
现在不是2003年
It's not 2003.
你对男同在派对上行为的看法也太老旧了
You have a very clichéd view of what gay men do at a party.
我们一起行动...
♪ We all move together... ♪
这又是什么应用来着？
What app is this for again?
这是我公司推出的一个新的勾搭应用
It's this new hookup app my company is launching.
我们已经有了Grindr 也有了Tinder
We've got Grindr. We've got Tinder.
这是Zellweger
This is Zellweger.
是为那些只想谈论女演员的男同准备的
It's for gay guys who just want to talk about actresses
然后上床睡觉  噢 那我用得上
then go to bed.  Oh, I'd use that.
鲍比 我和一个65岁的人做爱了
Bobby, I had sex with a 65 year old.
65岁？
Sixty five?
他的资料上没有写年龄
He didn't have an age on his profile.
他真的很好 他身体好到惊人
He was really nice, he had an amazing body
但他有 大白胡子
but he had this, like, big, white beard.
我觉得自己就像圣诞奶奶
I felt like Mrs. Claus.
我有点喜欢这样
I kind of love that.
这就是那个叫亚伦的家伙
There's that guy Aaron.
一起
♪ Together, together, together ♪
我们都在一起舞动
♪ We all move together ♪
一起
♪ Together, together ♪
我们都舞动起来...
♪ We all move... ♪
噢 我不知道那是谁
Oh, yeah, I don't know who that is.
他有时在健身房里
He's at the gym sometimes.
非常辣 也非常无聊
Very hot. Very boring.
噢 还有什么新鲜事？
Oh, what else is new?  Oh.
还有 今天我和一个男的做爱 他尿我身上了
Also, today I had sex with a guy who peed on me.
噢 你喜欢这样吗？
Oh, are you into that?
不太喜欢 但我还能做什么呢？
Not really, but what else was I doing?
也对
Fair enough.
说实话 这有点无聊
It was honestly kind of boring.
嘿 怎么样？
Hey, what's up?
嘿
Hey.
你好 亚伦
Well, hello, Aaron.  Hey.
这是鲍比
This is Bobby.
你们需要再喝一杯吗？
Do you boys need another drink?
我要去喝点喷射物 喷射物是什么鬼东西？
I'm getting a shitrocket.  What the hell's a shitrocket?
跟红牛差不多 但含有蛋白质
It's like a Red Bull but with protein.
噢
Oh.
那给我来喷射物加伏特加
Shitrocket and vodka, I guess.
闪开 男同们 Daddy需要去喝一杯
Move, boys. Daddy needs a drink.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你看起来很生气
You look angry.
我吗？
Me?
嗯 我没有
Well, I'm not.
我一直都这个样子
That's just the way I look.
我知道 人们总是跑来跟我说这些
I know. People always come up to me and tell me that
但我没有
but I'm not.
我没有生气
I'm not angry.
我有听你的播客
I listen to your podcast.
噢 真的吗？
Oh, really?
挺好的
Oh, that's cool.
我听说你很无趣
I hear you're boring.
谁说的？我才不无趣
Who said that? I'm not boring.
我不知道
I don't know.
很多人都这么说
A lot of people.
酷
Cool.
抱歉 有点尖酸刻薄了
I'm sorry. That was mean.
我很不擅长调情
I'm very bad at flirting.
而且我也是那种会告诉你我在调情的人
And I'm also the type of person who tells you I'm flirting
还挺性感的
which is so sexy.
没关系的
It's okay.
你是做什么的？
What do you do?
呃 工作方面？
Uh, for work?
我做遗嘱认证法 我是一名遗产规划师
I do probate law. I'm an estate planner.
总的来说 我帮人们写遗嘱的
Basically, I write people's wills.
你喜欢这个工作吗？ 噢 当然
Do you like it?  Oh, sure.
当我还是个孩子的时候 当我遇到一个人的时候
When I was a kid, first thing I would think
我想的第一件事就是
when I would meet someone is, "Who's that person
"这个人死后会把他的东西留给谁？
gonna leave their shit to when they die?"
我真的很想参与其中的法律后勤工作
I really wanted to be part of the legal logistics of that.
挺有趣的
That's funny.
那个人很性感 不是吗？
That guy's hot, right?
噢 是的
Oh, yeah. He is.
我等等应该要去操他和他老公
I'm supposed to fuck him and his husband later.
酷
Cool.
很好
Very good.
噢 我喜欢这首歌 叫什么来着？
Oh, I love this song.  What is this?
旧式的玛丽亚
Old school Mariah.
你怎么会不知道？
How do you not know this?
我比较喜欢乡村音乐
I'm more of a country guy.
比如 加思·布鲁克斯
You know, like Garth Brooks.
加思·布鲁克斯？
Garth Brooks?
你到底是谁？
Who are you?
我不想放手 虽然我应该放手的
♪ I don't wanna let go and although I should ♪
我不能离开你 因为... ...
♪ I can't leave you alone 'cause... ♪
事实上 凯莉·安德伍德在Twitter上屏蔽了我...
Actually, Carrie Underwood blocked me on Twitter...
我无法抗拒...
♪ And I cannot resist... ♪
什么鬼？？
What the fuck?
他到底去哪儿了？ 我不知道
Where the fuck did he go?  I don't know.
这就是为什么我讨厌这些人
This is why I hate these people.
噢 我的天 那个就是65岁那位
Oh, my God. That's the 65 year old.
天哪 他身材真的很好
Jesus, he's ripped.
是啊 就好像是他们注射类固醇到邓布利多身上
I know. It's like they injected steroids into Dumbledore.
嘿 怎么样？
Hey, what's up?
谢谢  嘿
Thanks.  Hey.
你去哪了？
Where'd you go?
我不知道 哪也没去
I don't know. Nowhere.
就是这样 尽情享受吧 女王们！
Yas, live your lives, queens!
Okurrrr.
Okurrr.
男同们太傻了
Gay guys are so stupid.
噢 我的天  我同意
Oh, my God, I know.
男同们通常  要么是非常聪明的
Gay guys are usually, like, the absolute smartest
要么就是 我见过的最愚蠢的人
or, like, the dumbest people I've ever met.
我们非常聪明 把
We've been smart enough to brand ourselves
聪明和机灵作为我们的代名词
as being smart and clever.
我曾经勾搭过一些人
I've hooked up with guys
事后我就会开个玩笑
and afterwards I'll make a joke
或者我说一些讽刺性的话
or I'll say something sarcastic.
而这家伙根本不明白我是在开玩笑
And the guy does not understand that I'm making a joke.
根本就不明白讽刺的意味
Literally does not understand satire.
我懂
I know.
异性恋认为我们都很聪明
And straight people think we're all smart
但很多人都是蠢得要命  是的
but a lot of these guys are dumb as shit.  Yes.
这是我们的小秘密
It's our little secret.
其实...
Actually...
你他妈的是在跟我开玩笑吗？
Are you fucking kidding me?
嘿 嘿 你和亚伦说了什么？
Hey.  Hey, what were you talking
聊了那么久
to Aaron about for so long?
就是关于很多男同的
Just about how a lot of gay guys
暗地里非常愚蠢
are secretly incredibly stupid.
噢 真是太妙了  我不明白
Oh, how fabulous.  I don't understand.
我们聊得很开心 然后他就玩失踪了
We're having a good time, and then he ghosts me.
就他妈的消失了
He just fucking disappears.
鲍比 别这样 随他去吧 他是个混蛋
Bobby, don't. Let it go. He's a dick.
不 我不会放任他的 我从来不会把事情置若惘然
No, I am not letting it go. I do not let things go.
你为什么不跳舞？ 我在跳舞 好吗？
Why aren't you dancing?  I am dancing, okay?
你想让我做什么 他妈的胡桃夹子组曲？
What do you want me to do, the fucking Nutcracker Suite?
嘿
Hey.
嘿 怎么了？
Hey, what's up?
我想吻你
I tried to kiss you
而你却没有回吻我 这就是问题所在
and you didn't kiss me back is what's up.
抱歉 我很害羞
I'm sorry. I'm shy.
求你了 你喜欢什么？
Please. What are you into?
这些无趣 身材好 但没有任何看法的白痴？
One of these boring, ripped idiots with no opinions?
不 我喜欢那种娇弱
No, I'd like someone who's physically very frail
又不停地讲话的人
and won't stop talking.
跟我回家吧
Come home with me.
我不能
I can't.
为什么？
Why?
因为你要和那个假棒球运动员
'Cause you have to fuck the fake baseball player
以及他的丈夫上床 ？
and his husband?
我不知道该和你说些什么
I don't know what to tell you.
再见了  喂 等等 等等
Goodbye.  Hey, wait, wait.
记一下我的号码  绝对不行
Take my number.  Absolutely not.
为什么？
Why?
因为我是聪明人之一 混蛋
'Cause I'm one of the smart ones, asshole.
噢 你是爱无能的人吗？
Oh, are you emotionally unavailable?
没有人比我更爱无能了
No one's more emotionally unavailable than me.
没有人 我以此为荣
No one. I pride myself on that.
不管怎样 这并不重要
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
亨利有我的电话号码
Henry has my number.
Grindr或Zellweger见
See you on Grindr or Zellweger
或者不管下一个APP是什么鬼东西
or whatever the fuck the next one is.
我都不玩那些
I'm not on any of those.
那你是怎么认识人的？
Then how do you meet people?
我不是真的在找
I'm not really looking.
是的
Yeah.
我也没有
Me neither.
对不起 打扰一下 借过一下
Excuse me. Excuse me.
请原谅我
Excuse me.
哦 我的天 他们voguing根本停不下来
Oh, my God, they cannot stop voguing.
他们voguing根本停不下来！
They cannot stop voguing!
请原谅我
Excuse me.
我知道你在voguing 但可以让我回家吗？求你了！
I know you're voguing, but can I please go home? Please?!
我有一种直觉
I had a gut feeling
你现在应该在线
you would be online now.
嗨
Hi.
嘿 怎么样？
Hey, what's up?
没什么 你呢？
Not much. You?
没有
No.
但我们匿名发短信给对方
But us texting each other anonymously.
我从来没有意识到Grindr是多么的
I never realized how much Grindr was
像《电子情书》 笑脸
just like You've Got Mail. Smiley face.
哈哈 大笑 鸡巴照片？
Ha ha. LOL. Dick pic?
没有鸡巴照片 不好意思
No dick pic. Sorry.
想想《电子情书》吧
Think about You've Got Mail.
梅格·瑞恩永远不会给你发一张她的生殖器照片
Meg Ryan would never send you a picture of her genitalia.
哈哈 笑死了 我能看看你的屁股吗？
Ha ha. LOLOL. Can I see your ass?
没有屁股照片 不好意思
Don't have ass pic. Sorry.
但我还是要看到屁股照片
Need to see ass pic, though.
没有屁股照片!
Don't have ass pic!
不会去见面的
Not gonna meet up
除非你发屁股的照片
unless you send ass pic.
必须看到屁股的照片！
Must see pic of ass!
嗷！
Ow!
操！
Fuck!
我流血了！
I'm bleeding!
我现在要怎么拉屎呢？
How am I gonna shit now?
我不能做爱 我不能拉屎
I can't fuck. I can't shit.
不想活了 该死的！
I'm not a person, goddamn it!
太他妈的平了
It's too fucking flat.
这是为你拍的 哥们
Took this just for you, bro.
他拉黑我了吗？
Did he block me?
操你妈的！
Motherfucker!
霍尔心荣幸为你呈现
Hallheart proudly presents
我们的第一部双性恋节日电影：
our first bisexual holiday film
获奖的 "双性恋圣诞"
the award winning Christmas with Either.
霍尔心 总是走在圣诞的...
Hallheart. Always on the cutting edge...
最前沿
of Christmas.
大伙
People. Okay.
好了  大伙！
Okay, people!
大伙！现在已经很晚了
People, please! It's getting late.
我们仍然需要找到一个捐赠者来资助
We still need to find a donor to fund
最后一翼的展览
the exhibit in the final wing.
如你所知 1号码头家具本应提供
As you know, Pier 1 Imports was supposed to make
大笔捐款 但他们破产了
a big donation, but they went bankrupt
并被塔利班收购
and have been bought by the Taliban.
塔利班
Taliban.
因此 我们缺少500万美元
So, we are short $5 million.
我们不能再次推迟我们的开幕
We cannot afford to push our opening again.
人们会认为我们有麻烦了
People will think we're in trouble.
也许这整个地方都会垮掉
Maybe this whole place could fall apart.
我们需要对最后一间侧厅的内容有新的想法
We need new ideas for what goes in the final wing
而且是现在就需要
and we need them now.
彻丽 你说  你知道挂在
Cherry, go.  You know the blue whale
自然历史博物馆的那条蓝鲸吗？
hanging in the Museum of Natural History?
知道  怎么了
Yes.  What about that
但如果不是蓝鲸 而是一位女同性恋呢？
but instead of the blue whale, it's a lesbian?
噢 不 呃  呃
Oh, no. Uh uh.  Yeah, okay.
好吧 我们不能这么做  不行
Well, yeah, we can't do that.  No.
那一位来自原住民国家的变性女人呢？
What about a transgender woman from an Indigenous nation?
该死的 万达！
Goddamn it, Wanda!
那四百个参加内战的
What about the 400 lesbians
女同性恋者呢？
who fought in the Civil War?
闭嘴吧 彻丽 她们并不都是女同性恋
Shut up, Cherry. They were not all lesbians.
他们中的一些人是变性人
Some of them were trans men.
好了 别说了 这座建筑是一个难得的机会
Okay, stop. This building is a rare chance
使双性恋者的历史合法化
to legitimize the history of bisexuals.
噢 我的天 又开始了
Oh, God. Here we go.
是的! 我们说 "LGBTQ"
Yes! We say "LGBTQ,"
但我们总是跳过 "B"
but we always skip over the "B."
我想要一个双性恋者的大厅
I want a hall of bisexuals
就像迪士尼的总统大厅
like Disney's Hall of Presidents.
我想要一个充满动画的舞台 会说话的双性恋者
I want a stage full of animatronic, talking bisexuals.
会说话、会动、会做手势的双性恋者
Talking and moving and gesturing bisexuals.
你知道吗？
You know what?
这周恰好是双性恋意识周
This happens to be Bisexual Awareness Week
但没有人意识到这一点
and no one has acknowledged it!
我知道  这倒是真的 我的错
I acknowledged.  That is true. My bad.
女同性恋历史月是在三月
Lesbian History Month was in March.
怎么没有人说过什么呢！
Nobody said a goddamn thing!
现在是六月！
It's June!
那是在三月！
It was in March!
当然 女同性恋者有一个月的时间 而我们有一个星期
Of course lesbians get a month and we get a week.
罗伯特  什么？
Robert.  What?
我想让你知道 我听到了你的声音
I want you to know that I hear you.
我看到你了 我想为你保留空间
I see you, and I'm holding space for you.
她来了 她来了
There she go. There she go.
她从来没有自己的任何想法
She never has any ideas of her own
但她总是在 "保留空间"
but she's always "holding space."
一位女同性恋者写了 "美丽的美国"
A lesbian wrote "America the Beautiful."
天哪 不 我不能  凯萨琳·李·贝茨
God, no. I can't.  Katharine Lee Bates
把歌词写在一张餐巾纸上
wrote the lyrics on a napkin.
如果你去她在弗吉尼亚州的房子 他们有那张餐巾纸!
If you go to her house in Virginia, they have the napkin!
如果最后的展品是
What if the final exhibit was
重现一位酷儿的婚礼？
a recreation of a queer wedding?
我喜欢这样  好吧 那我不讨厌
I like that.  Okay, that I don't hate.
塔玛拉 那真是太甜蜜了
Tamara, that is so sweet.
我喜欢这样 而且人们可以
I love that. And people can
来这里登记 领取结婚礼物
come and register for wedding gifts here.
我要把这个写下来
I'm gonna write that down.
噢 我的天   不！
Oh, my God, and  No!
那是老式的
That is old fashioned
异性恋的毫无意义的东西
heteronormative nonsense.
我们需要通过酷儿的棱镜
We need to get people to rethink history
让人们重新思考历史 而不是用另一个该死的同性恋婚礼
through a queer prism, not comfort them
去抚慰他们 好吗？
with another fucking gay wedding, all right?
这是个博物馆 不是《富家穷路》
It's a museum. It's not Schitt's Creek.
噢 我喜欢《富家穷路》  但是我
Ooh, I like Schitt's Creek.  But I
但是我爱《富家穷路》
Oh, I love Schitt's Creek.
那个节目是有层次的  好吧
That show has layers.  All right.
每个人都喜欢《富家穷路》很好 好的
Everyone loves Schitt's Creek. Great. Okay.
这就是你们让我想起的人 尤金·列维
That's who you remind me of. Eugene Levy.
是的
Yes.
好的 芬克先生
Okay, Mr. Funk.
我今天能帮你什么吗？
How can I help you today?
我需要调整我的遗嘱
I need to adjust my will.
好的 我可以问你为什么吗？
Okay. Can I ask you why?
因为我快死了
Because I'm dying.
我得了癌症
I have cancer.
听到这个消息我很难过
I'm so sorry to hear that.
我只是需要弄清楚我的钱的去处
I just need to figure out where my money's going.
好吧 呃 你有伴侣或配偶吗？
Okay, uh, do you have a partner or spouse?
没有 没有
No and no.
孩子？ 没有
Children?  No.
家庭成员？ 没有
Family member?  No.
亲密的朋友？ 不再是了
Close friend?  Not anymore.
好吧 嗯...
Okay, um...
嗯 呃 有时候闭上眼睛会有帮助
well, uh, sometimes it helps to close your eyes
想一想 在这个世界上 谁对你来说是最重要的
and think about who means the most to you in the world.
呃 是谁呢？
Uh, who is it?
雪儿
Cher.
好的 所以你想留下10万美元...
Okay, so you want to leave $100,000...
给雪儿？
to Cher?
你真的认为她需要这些吗？
Do you really think that she needs that?
她员工太多了
She has a huge staff.
呃 好的.
Uh, okay.
谢泼德先生 呃   抱歉打扰了
Mr. Shepard, uh  Sorry to interrupt.
贝利夫人去世了
Mrs. Bailey passed away.
噢 我的天 这太令人沮丧了
Oh, God, this is so depressing.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
你正在经历的这一切我唯能想象
I can only imagine what you're going through.
不 我是说你的工作
No, I mean your job.
真让人沮丧
What a downer.
是亚伦 Grindr用得怎么样了？
It's Aaron. How's Grindr?
虚无的东西 我花了45分钟
A dream. I spent 45 minutes
拍了一张我自己的屁股
taking a picture of my own ass.
你怎么样？
How are you?
和那个芝加哥小熊的群交怎么样？
How was group sex with that faux Chicago Cub?
很有趣 他们邀请我明天再来
It was fun. They invited me back tomorrow.
他们的代孕妈妈怀孕了
Their surrogate is pregnant
他们要举行性别揭秘狂欢
and they're having a gender reveal orgy.
揭示性别的狂欢？
A gender reveal orgy?
詹姆斯·鲍德温会感到非常自豪
James Baldwin would be so proud.
大笑 我笑着醒来 因为
LOL. I woke up laughing about
你如此无礼地数落了我一顿
you so rudely calling me out on my shit.
嗯 你活该 婊子
Well, you deserved it, bitch.
说实话 我很佩服
Honestly, I was impressed.
你可能比我更爱无能
You may be more emotionally unavailable than I am.
好吧 也许我们可以
Well, maybe we can be
爱无能地在一起
emotionally unavailable together.
"也许我们可以
"Maybe we can be
一起爱无能"？
emotionally unavailable together"?
谁在帮你发短信？Maroon 5？
Who's writing your texts? Maroon 5?
滚一边去  开玩笑的！
Fuck off.  Kidding!
我们可以一起出去玩 你要约我出去吗？
We can go out. Are you asking me out?
我很乐意  是的 我也一样
I'm down for whatever.  Yeah, same.
很好  听起来不错
Cool.  Sounds good.
那么 明天？或者我们可以做任何事情
So, tomorrow? Or we can do whatever.
好 我什么时候都可以 也可以做任何事
Yeah, I can do whenever, and I can do whatever.
我不在乎我们做什么  是啊 我也不在乎
I don't care what we do.  Yeah, me neither.
我们可以做任何事 而且随时都可以做
We can do whatever, and we can do it whenever.
这对你有用吗？ 是的 这绝对有效
Does that work for you?  Yeah, that definitely works.
太好了 无论做什么 什么时候都可以
Great. Whatever, whenever.
酷  随便
Cool. Whatever, whenever.
迈克尔·斯科特跳舞的GIF
GIF of Michael Scott dancing.
他很不错
He's good.
《办公室》的GIF？
Office GIF?
这个人不是同性恋
This person isn't gay.
心心 呃 算
Heart. Ugh, no.
不心心 竖起大拇指
Un heart. Thumbs up.
和平  和平？
Peace.  Peace?
稍后
Later.
你能在later后发个心心吗 婊子？
Can you heart my "later," bitch?
再见
Bye.
你是这里人 对吗？
You're from here, right?
你的父母还住在这儿？
Your parents still live in the city?
不 实际上我的父母都去世了
No. My parents both passed away actually.
噢 对不起   没错 谢谢
Oh, I'm sorry.  Oh, yeah. Thanks.
好久之前了
It wasn't recent.
我妈妈在我上大学的时候就去世了
My mom died when I was in college
而我的父亲十年前就去世了
and my dad died like ten years ago.
蜜蜂！
A bee! A bee! A bee!
蜜蜂！ 啊啊啊啊啊！
A bee! A bee! A bee!  Whoa, whoa, whoa!
别拍了 你会杀了它的
Stop swatting. You're gonna kill it.
嗯 这就是我想做的
Well, that's what I'm trying to do.
它在我的脖子上
It's on my neck.
蜜蜂要灭绝了 你不看书的吗？
The bees are dying. Don't you read?
看啊 都是些关于同性恋的东西和电影
Yes, about gay stuff and movies.
你能做点什么吗？
Can you, like, do something?  Yes.
对对对 就在这里
Yes, yes, yes, yes. Here it is.
你直接碰到它了！ 我知道
You're touching the bee!  I know.
好的
Okay.
哇 谢谢你
Wow. Thank you.
你就像成人版的同性恋童子军
You're like a grown up gay Boy Scout
而我就像埃文·汉森最后发生的一切
and I'm like whatever ends up happening to Evan Hansen.
让我看看在放什么
Let me see what's playing.
你一直以来最喜欢的电影是什么？
What's your favorite movie of all time?
我最喜欢的电影是什么？
What's my favorite movie of all time?
我也说不好
I don't know.
为什么？你最喜欢的电影是什么？
Why? What's your favorite movie?
《宿醉》
The Hangover.
《宿醉》是你一直以来最喜欢的电影？
The Hangover is your favorite movie of all time?
你看过多少部电影？一部？
How many movies have you seen? One?
它还挺有趣的 行吧 算是吧
It's a funny movie.  Yeah, kinda.
你还记得那部电影的前面的台词之一吗？
And you remember one of the first lines of that movie?
"呼叫基佬博士"
"Paging Dr. Faggot."
记得吗？ 是的
Remember that?  Yes.
"呼唤基佬博士 "是2009年收入
"Paging Dr. Faggot" is one of the first lines
最高的喜剧片的台词之一
of the highest grossing comedy of 2009
然而 没有人谈论它
and and no one talks about it.
不是吗？而且这也不是很久以前的事了
Right? And it wasn't that long ago.
你知道 我们只是应该 一笑置之
You know, we're just supposed to, like, laugh it off.
这并不困扰我 我不是那种敏感的人
It doesn't bother me. I'm not sensitive like that.
我认为你只是喜欢发怒
I think you just like getting angry at things.
发怒是你的代名词
Getting angry at things is, like, your brand.
什么？不 不是的！去你妈的！
What?! No, it's not! Fuck you!
发怒是我的代名词？
Getting angry at things is my brand?
不 不 不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
你只是不喜欢抱怨而已
You just don't like to complain about it
因为那意味着你的感情受到了伤害
because that means your feelings were hurt
而这意味着承认你是弱者
and that means admitting you're weak.
而 那显得太脆弱了
And that's too vulnerable.
就像我们到处说
And as much as we go around saying
男人应该是脆弱的 你我都知道
men should be vulnerable, you and I both know
那是胡说八道
that is such bullshit.
因为对很多这些同性恋者来说
Because for a lot of these gay guys
甜美和脆弱是美妙可爱的
sweetness and vulnerability are wonderful and lovely
但它们也可能成为真正的勃起杀手
but they can also be a real boner killer.
你非常紧张
You're very intense.
是的
Yes.
顺便说一下 我是在开玩笑  关于什么？
I was kidding, by the way.  About what?
《宿醉》 那不是我最喜欢的电影
The Hangover. It's not my favorite movie.
不 不可能  是的 我是在开玩笑
No, you weren't.  Yeah, I was.
我只是喜欢看你被激怒
I just like seeing you get riled up.
我不相信你  我是在开玩笑
I don't believe you.  I was kidding.
嗯
Hmm.
我不喜欢这样
I don't like this.
好吧 让我们看看我们这里有什么
Okay. Let's see what we have here.
嗯 嗯
Mm hmm.
噢 《内心的宝藏》
Oh, The Treasure Inside
实际上 应该还是挺不错的
is supposed to be really good, actually.
那是关于什么的？
What's that about?
它是关于在1849年加州淘金热中的两个未出柜的
It's about two closeted gay frontiersmen
男同拓荒者的故事
in the California Gold Rush of 1849.
但实际上 它是关于两个直男演员扮演同性恋
But really it's about two straight actors playing gay
试图赢得奥斯卡奖
trying to win an Oscar.
我从来没有厌倦过
I never tire of watching two very straight actors
看两个非常直的演员 真正把自己变成多情善感的同性恋
really transform themselves into being sad and gay.
同性恋演员扮演同性恋  根本就不叫演戏
Gay actors playing gay  that's not even acting.
噢 我完全同意
Oh, I totally agree.
如果他们拍一部关于我的生活的电影
If they ever make a movie about my life
他们最好雇一个直男演员
they better hire a straight actor.
我喜欢把我的人生故事看作是
I like to think of my life story as
本尼迪克特·康伯巴奇能拿奖的又一部电影
just another way for Benedict Cumberbatch to really score.
好吧 如果我们不看这部电影 我们该怎么办呢？
Okay, if we don't see this movie, what are we gonna do?
我没有说我不想看这部电影
Well, I didn't say I didn't want to see the movie.
噢  我会去看那该死的电影的
Oh.  I'll see the fucking movie.
我很想看
I'm dying to.
我认为它比《请以你的名字呼唤我》要好多了
I'd put it way above Call Me by Your Name
但略低于《达拉斯买家俱乐部》
but sort of below Dallas Buyers.
好吧 它还是俘获我的芳心了
Well, it got me in the end.
但为什么总是要那么悲惨？
Yeah, but why does it always have to be so tragic?
我不知道 《费城故事》《米尔克》《断背山》
I don't know. Philadelphia, Milk, Brokeback.
快乐的结局并不能赢得奥斯卡奖
Happy endings don't win Oscars.
异性恋喜欢看我们悲惨的样子
Straight people love seeing us miserable.
等等 亚伦·谢泼德？
Mm.  Wait, Aaron Shepard?
乔什·埃文斯?
Josh Evans?
我靠！怎么样 伙计？ 嘿 伙计 兄弟！
Holy shit! What is up, dude?  Hey, man. Bro!
很高兴见到你  已经他妈的有一段时间了
Nice to see you.  It's been for fucking ever.
亚伦和我... ... 我们在高中时打过曲棍球
Aaron and I  we played hockey in high school.
这是我的未婚妻Samantha
This is my fiancée Samantha.
嘿 很高兴见到你  嘿
Hey. Nice to meet you.  Hey.
呃 这位是 呃 鲍比
Uh, this is, uh, Bobby.
嘿
Hey.  Hey.
我们刚看了《内心的宝藏》
We just saw The Treasure Inside.
是关于未出柜的男同拓荒者的
It's about closeted gay frontiersmen.
噢 好的 不错
Oh. Okay. Nice.
这只是 一些愚蠢的电影
It's just, like, some dumb movie.
噢 等等 我想看这个
Oh, wait. I want to see that.
同性恋是我的菜
Gay guys are my jam.
嗯
Hmm.
那么 你们在这里做什么？
So what are you guys doing here?
只是一次小小的旅行
Just a little trip.
这是她第一次来纽约市
It's her first time in New York City.
这座城市太酷啦
This city is sick.
真的是  是啊
It really is.  Yeah.
嗯... 很好
Well... awesome.
是的  嗯 很高兴见到你 鲍勃
Yeah.  Uh, nice to meet you, Bob.
很高兴见到你们
Nice to meet you guys.
这很疯狂
That is crazy.
我从来没有碰到过我家乡的人
I never run into anybody from my hometown.
噢 是的 兄弟 完全正确 兄弟
Oh, yeah, bro. Totally, bro.
只是一些愚蠢的电影 兄弟
Just some dumb movie, bro.
我在高中时最迷恋他了
I had the biggest crush on him in high school.
好吧 同性恋的一贯作风
Yep. That tracks.
嗯 就像《马戏之王》中的大胡子女士
Well, like the bearded lady in The Greatest Showman
这就是我
this is me.
哦
Oh.
那个芝加哥小熊？
The faux Chicago Cub?
是的 他的丈夫刚给我发了这个
Yeah. His husband just sent me that.
哇 他们非常火辣
Wow. They are extremely hot.
是啊 迈克和道格... 他们是这些类固醇傻瓜
Yeah, Mike and Doug  they're these roided out meatheads.
他们不是最亮眼的 但他们真的很可爱
They're not the brightest, but they're really sweet.
你想去那里吗？
Do you want to go over there?
等等 你是不是又要甩掉我
Wait. Are you ditching me again
去干那个棒球运动员和他的丈夫？
to go fuck the baseball cosplayer and his husband?
不 我不是在抛弃你 我是在邀请你
No, I'm not ditching you. I'm inviting you.
你为什么不直接上楼来？
Why don't you just come upstairs?
啊 我不太擅长做恋爱关系的整套事情
Ah, I don't really do the whole relationship thing very well.
恋爱关系？
Relationship?
我什么时候说过我想和你谈恋爱了？
When did I say I wanted to be in a relationship with you?
我们也就出去了一天
We literally hung out one day.
是的 但如果我上楼去
Yeah, but if I go upstairs
就会变成 整套事情...
it becomes, like, a whole thing and...
不管怎么样 我们应该去那里
Whatever. We should just go over there.
很有意思的
It'll be fun.
我不会去的 但你应该去
I'm not gonna go, but you should go.
但我可以问你一件事吗？
Can I ask you one thing, though?
如果你不想约 为什么给我发短信？
Why did you text me if you didn't want to hook up?
我没有生气 我只是真的很好奇
I'm not angry. I'm just honestly curious.
我没有说我不想... 我...
I didn't say I didn't want to  I...
我想我在俱乐部里和你聊天很开心
I guess I had fun talking to you at the club
我只是想问问你怎么样了
and I wanted to say, "Hey, what's up?"
"嘿 怎么样了？"
"Hey, what's up?"
所以 总的来说 你给我发短信的时侯宿醉了
So, basically you texted me when you were feeling hungover
觉得寂寞 但你实际上并不喜欢我
and lonely in that moment, but you're not actually into me
但你还是去参加了约会
but you went on the date anyway.
为什么男同这么奇怪？
Why are gay guys so weird?
实际上 你知道 我们并不奇怪
Actually, you know, we're not weird.
我们只是不断迎合自己的奇思妙想和需求
We're just constantly catering to our own whims and needs
这可以在一瞬间改变 但我们甚至从未考虑过
which can change on a dime, but we never even think about
对方的情感后果
the emotional consequences of the other person.
总之 迎合你的奇思妙想是件很愉快的事
Anyway, it's been a blast catering to your whims.
而且 说实话 我真的不能说什么
And, honestly, I can't really say anything about it
因为我一直在对别人做同样的事情 所以......
because I do the same thing to people all the time, so...
有趣的一天 还有 嗯....有趣的一天
Fun day. And, um...  Fun day.
和那些人玩得开心
Yeah.  Have fun with those guys.
好的 再见
Okay. Bye.
鲍比 等等
Bobby, wait.
当你带着一颗破碎的心做梦的时候... ...
♪ When you're dreaming with a broken heart... ♪
我今天过得非常愉快
I had a really nice time today.
我也是
Me, too.
我从来不去约会 但那真的很有趣
I never go on dates, but that was really fun.
是的 我也玩得很开心
Yeah. I had a really good time, too.
嘿 我要走了
Hey, I'm gonna go.
哦 真的？
Oh, really?
是啊
Yeah.
一切都好吗？这很奇怪吗？
Is everything okay? Is this weird?
哦 不 不 不 不 这很有趣 非常棒
Oh, no, no, no. No, it's fun. It's great.
我只是   我只是要走了
I just  I'm just gonna go.
好吧 好吧 再见了
Okay.  Okay. I'll see you.
好的 再见  好的
Okay. Bye.  Okay.
再见
Bye.
嘿 伙计们 我得走了 非常感谢你们
Hey, guys, I'm gonna go. Thank you so much.
不 你要走了？ 是的 我得走了
No. You're leaving?  Yeah, I got to go.
好的 伙计 很高兴认识你
All right, man. It was nice meeting you.
是啊 你也是 这很美好  是的
Yeah, you, too. It was lovely.  Yeah.
谢谢你  好的 晚安
Thank you.  All right. Good night.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
谢谢你的到来 我们确信布莱恩是同性恋
Thanks for coming. We're convinced Brian's gay
我认为有他的同性恋叔叔在身边对他来说是件好事
and I think it's good for him to have his gay uncle around.
噢 我的天 当然了
Oh, my God. Of course.
我这个gay叔叔一直都会在我gay侄子有需要的时候出现的
I'm always here to be a good "guncle" to my "g nephew."
噢 鲍比叔叔 你能看看我的报告吗？
Aw.  Uncle Bobby, will you read my report?
是关于佛莱迪·摩克瑞的
It's about Freddie Mercury.
他对《波西米亚狂想曲》很着迷
He's obsessed with Bohemian Rhapsody.
噢 我的天 我喜欢这个
Oh, my God, I love this.
就像那部电影一样 你的报告是否将一个关于伟大的同性恋偶像的故事
And like that movie, does your report take a story
变成关于他可能有一次
about one of the great gay icons and make it about
与一个女人发生性关系？
that one time he maybe had sex with a woman?
我以为佛莱迪·摩克瑞是双性恋
I thought Freddie Mercury was bi.
他有一个妻子
He had a wife.
是的 耶稣也是如此 但他是同性恋
Yeah, well, so did Jesus, and he was gay.
这很好 是对电影的一种改进
This is excellent and an improvement on the film.
做得好！"
Good job!
那些《宿醉》的GIF是什么？
What are those GIFs from The Hangover?
没什么
Nothing.
和我约会的这个家伙不停地给我发短信
This guy I went out with won't stop texting me.
一个男人？真的吗？
A guy? Really?
你是说Grindr上的家伙？ 不 令人震惊的是
Like a Grindr guy?  No, shockingly.
我实际上在现实生活中遇到了这个人
I actually met this one in real life.
鲍比！
Bobby!
那真是太棒了！
That's fantastic!
你觉得你会再见到他吗？
You think you're gonna see him again?
不 他告诉我他更喜欢群交 而不是一对一
No. He told me he prefers group sex
因为一对一太紧张了
to one on one because one on one is too intense
会让人感觉在做谈恋爱的全套事情
and makes it a whole thing.
我们就约会了一次 然后就和三个人发生了关系
We went on one date, and we had sex with three people.
现在的同性恋关系就像一辆小丑车
Gay relationships these days are like a clown car.
噢 又来了一个 噢 看 还有一个
Oh, there's another one. Oh, look, another one.
噢 又来一个？这很荒唐
Oh, another one? It's ridiculous.
另外 我不认为我是他喜欢的类型
Plus, I don't think I'm his type.
你怎么知道？ 因为我知道
How do you know?  Because I know.
他告诉我他喜欢乡村音乐
He told me he likes country music
他最喜欢的歌手是加思·布鲁克斯
and his favorite singer is Garth Brooks.
什么样的同性恋会说
What kind of gay man says
他最喜欢的歌手是加思·布鲁克斯？
his favorite singer is Garth Brooks?
这让我感到害怕
That scares me.
另外 我看到他喜欢的那些人
Plus, I see the guys he likes.
他们都和他长得一模一样
They all look exactly like him.
他们都是 大块头 火辣 看起来很直的
They're all these, like, big, hot, straight acting dudes.
根本与我搭不上边
It's just not me.
那么 他是1还是0？
Well, is he a top or bottom?
这有什么关系呢？
What does that have to do with anything?
也许你们都是0 这就是问题所在
Maybe you're both bottoms, and that's the problem.
我也能做1的 埃德加
I'm not always the bottom, Edgar.
〇动起来！
Bottom dance!
噢 〇动起来
Ooh, bottom dance!  Yeah!
噢 我的天
Oh, my God.
同性恋性行为还是当直人对它
Gay sex was more fun
感到不舒服的时候更有趣
when straight people were uncomfortable with it.
操他妈的《富家穷路》
Fucking Schitt's Creek.
也许我们应该在你的孩子面前
Maybe we should stop talking about
停止谈论肛交
anal sex in front of your children.
不 拜托 这是自然生活的一部分
Nah.  Oh, please. It's a natural part of life.
鲍比 再约他出来 你从不喜欢任何人
Bobby, ask him out again. You never like anyone.
他是如此的英俊
He is so handsome.
你也是  你 你是个辣哥
So are you.  Y You're a hottie.
他是另一个层面上的 他就像同性恋版的汤姆·布雷迪
He is, like, on another level. He's like gay Tom Brady.
当我和他在一起的时候 我感觉就像该死的坏女巫
When I'm with him, I feel like friggin' Elphaba.
我打赌他对你的威胁和你对他的威胁一样大
I bet he's as intimidated by you as you are by him.
噢 是的  我告诉你
Oh, yeah.  I'm telling you.
他只是害怕变得脆弱
He's just scared of being vulnerable.
你们这一代的同性恋
Gay guys from your generation
仍然有这些压抑的男子气概的问题
still have all these pent up masculinity issues
而你们都需要克服它
and you all just need to get over it already.
布莱恩班上有一半的孩子是不分性别的
Half the kids in Brian's class are nonbinary.
嗯 这不公平 蒂娜
Well, it's not fair, Tina.
我们有艾滋病 而他们有《欢乐合唱团》
We had AIDS, and they had Glee.
但有一件工作上的事
But there is a work thing
我在想也许可以邀请他参加
I was thinking of maybe inviting him to.
也许吧  什么 工作的事？
Maybe.  What, a work thing?
有很多名人和花哨的人那个？
With lots of celebrities and fancy people?
现在 你要用孔雀开屏来打动他吗？
Now, are you gonna peacock to impress him?
不 这只是一个大型筹款活动
No. It's just a big fundraiser
我需要带人来
for the museum, and I need to bring someone.
你会在舞台上吗？
Are you gonna be onstage?
不 我不打算上台 好吗？
No, I am not going to be onstage, okay?
我不是那种自恋的反社会主义者
I am not some sort of narcissistic sociopath.
谢谢你 豆荚猫
Thank you, Doja Cat.
各位 在津巴布韦有一些岩画
Everyone, there are rock paintings in Zimbabwe
描绘了同性恋的内容
which depict homosexuality
可以追溯到公元前2000年
that date back to the year 2000 BCE.
如果那些画上的人
If only the men on those paintings
能够再活4000年 看到《费城永远阳光灿烂》中的一个角色出柜
had lived another 4,000 years to see a character come out
那就好了
on It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia.
你的下巴是谁做的？
Who did your chin?
噢 不 我下巴是真的
Oh, no. It's real.
是的
Yeah.
我的也是
Mine, too.
请继续慷慨解囊 以便博物馆
Please continue to give generously so the museum
可以讲述这中间所有的故事
can tell all the stories in between
那些从未被讲述过的故事
that have never been told.
非常感谢你们 晚安
Thank you very much. Good night.
嘿 我很抱歉 我把你一个人留在这里
Hey, I'm so sorry I left you alone.
事情变得有点疯狂  不
Things got a little crazy.  No.
嘿 伙计 你  你 你真是太棒了
Hey, dude, you you were, you were awesome.
我的意思是 我永远也做不到这一点
I mean, I could never do that
在一群人面前那样说话  噢
speaking in front of a bunch of people like that.  Oh.
你的活动范围很广
You move in some pretty fancy circles.
我不知道
I had no idea.
噢 相信我 并不总是这么有魅力
Oh, trust me, it's not always this glamorous.
鲍比 惊人的一如既往  噢
Bobby, that was amazing, as always.  Oh.
谢谢你 查尔斯  恭喜你的一切
Thank you, Charles.  Congrats on everything.
非常感谢你 谢谢你的到来
Thank you so much. Thank you for coming.
谢谢你
Thank you.
伟大的演讲 鲍比
Great speech, Bobby.
非常感谢你
Thank you so much.
嘿 你想看看博物馆吗？
Hey, do you want to see the museum?
我可以给你一个私人参观  噢 当然
I can give you a private tour.  Oh, sure.
但我不想把你从这一切中拖走
I I don't want to drag you away from all this, though.
噢 没事的
Oh, no, it's fine.
这里 那边  好的
Here. That way.  Okay.
这里是传奇馆
This is The Legends Pavilion.
LGBTQ+历史上的无名英雄们
Unsung heroes from LGBTQ+ history.
玛莎·皮·约翰逊和西尔维娅·里维拉
Marsha P. Johnson and Sylvia Rivera.
通常情况下 石墙事件是唯一
Usually, Stonewall is the only thing
直人知道的关于同性恋的历史
straight people know about queer history.
说实话 没有人真正知道
Truthfully, no one really knows
谁在石墙事件上扔了第一块砖头
who threw the first bricks at Stonewall.
但是 正是像玛莎和西尔维娅这样的有色人种女性
But it was trans women of color like Marsha and Sylvia
她们推动了最早的同性恋解放运动的发展
who drove the earliest days of the queer liberation movement.
那么你怎么看？
So what do you think?
这很不可思议 对吗？
It's pretty incredible, right?
是的 我的意思是 它  它  它真的令人印象深刻
Yeah. I mean, it's it's it's really impressive.
但是呢？
But?
但是 这有点令人沮丧
But it's kind of depressing.
沮丧？它让你感到压抑？
It's depressing? It made you depressed?
都是些艾滋病、纳粹和恐同
It's AIDS and Nazis and homophobia.
所有这些都是挺压抑的
All of it's just  it's kind of a downer.
好吧  你在期待什么？
Okay. Well, what were you expecting?
《博物馆之夜》？
A Night at the Museum?
老实说 我的家人喜欢那部电影
Honestly, my family loves that movie.
哦 好吧
Oh, okay.
噢 如果你做这样的事情呢？
Oh, what if you did something like that?
那些... 那些东西它们活了过来
Where where the things, they come alive
比如说 对你说话
and they, like, talk at you.
"那些东西都活了过来 然后他们对你说话"？
"Where the things come alive, and they talk at you"?
是的  到底是什么？噢 噢
Yeah.  Like what exactly? Oh, oh.
如果我们有 比如：
What if we had, like
安娜·埃莉诺·罗斯福的半身像 对吗？
a bust of Eleanor Roosevelt, right?  Yeah.
当你走近了 然后突然间 你发现那不是
And you get really close, and then all of a sudden
安娜·埃莉诺·罗斯福
you realize that's not Eleanor Roosevelt.
那是艾米·舒默
It's Amy Schumer.
噢  不！
Oh.  No!
这是个博物馆 不应该是有趣的
It's a museum. It's not supposed to be fun.
鲍比
Bobby.
黛博拉·梅辛的经纪人在Zoom上等着我们了
We've got Debra Messing's agent on a Zoom.
这很紧急
It's urgent.
黛博拉担心她即将被脱粉
Debra's worried that she's on the verge of being canceled.
她在一次采访中说 她是
She said in an interview that she was
塔夫茨的维奥拉·戴维斯 人们很生气
the Viola Davis of Tufts, and people are mad.
她的经纪人说
Her agent is saying
她可能会给博物馆一笔非常大的捐款
that she may give a very big donation to the museum
以挽回面子
to save face.
谁是黛布拉·梅辛？
Who's Debra Messing?
来自《威尔与格雷斯》 噢 我的天
From Will & Grace. Oh, my God.
好的 等等 这真让人震惊
Yes.  Okay, wait. This is amazing.
是的  待在这里 我5分钟后回来
Yes.  Stay right here. I'll be back in five minutes.
当然   我们走吧  好的
Sure. Yep.  Let's go.  Okay.
亚伦？
Aaron?
搞什么鬼？
What the fuck?
向你哥哥问好  怎么样？  怎么样？
Say hi to your brother.  Sup?  Sup?
杰森要住在这里
Jason's staying here
当他决定好要住在哪里的时候
while he figures out where to live.
永远不要离婚 亚伦
Never get divorced, Aaron.
永远不要结婚  好的 妈妈
Never get married.  Okay, Mom.
我很抱歉 我在工作 我要先挂了
I'm sorry. I'm at work, so I I should probably get going.
哦 我差点忘了告诉你
Oh, I almost forgot to tell you.
你还记得乔希·埃文斯吗？
Do you remember Josh Evans?
是的 高中时的乔什·埃文斯
Yeah, Josh Evans from high school.
实际上 我前几天在街上碰到了
I actually ran into him and his fiancée
他和他的未婚妻
on the street the other day.
嗯 他们刚刚分手了 你想知道为什么吗？
Well, they just broke up. And you want to know why?
因为他是同性恋
Because he's gay.
乔希·埃文.   不
Josh Ev  No.
我感到非常尴尬
I'm definitely embarrassed
这事花了我这么长时间
about how long this has taken me
但我被告知人们在他们自己的时间里做这件事
but I'm told people do this in their own time.
我的英雄科尔顿·安德伍德给了我力量
I've been empowered by my hero, Colton Underwood
事实证明 我是同性恋
to say that, as it turns out, I'm gay.
如果你喜欢我是同性恋 就点赞这个帖子
And like this post if you like that I'm gay.
和平
Peace.
真他妈的
Holy shit.
所以我们开始来回走了一会儿
So we started going back and forth for a while
然后在最后 我就说：
and then at the end, I was just like
"你为什么不把专辑叫做《柠檬水》？"
"Why don't you call the album Lemonade?"
鲍比？
Bobby?
等你准备好了
When you're ready.
什么？  当你准备好的时候
What?  When you're ready.
对不起
Sorry.
好的 人们想知道
Okay. People wonder
美国是否已经准备好迎接它的第一位同性恋总统
if America is ready for its first gay president.
我说我们已经有一个了
I say we already had one.
对于最后一间侧厅 请考虑
For the final wing, please consider
《林肯的信》 一个美国同性恋的爱情故事
The Lincoln Letters: A Gay American Love Story.
多年来 历史学家一直
For years, historians have
对林肯的性取向进行猜测
speculated about Lincoln's sexuality.
他与多个男人同床共枕
He shared a bed and exchanged intimate letters with
并交换了亲密的信件 其中包括约书亚·斯比德
multiple men over the years, including Joshua Speed
以及大卫·德瑞克森 斯比德...  好吧 我必须阻止你
and David Derrickson. Speed...  Okay, I'm stopping you.
鲍比 这行不通 你不能说林肯是同性恋
Bobby, it won't work. You can't say Lincoln was gay.
为什么？ 没有办法确认
Why?  There's no way to confirm
那些只是性关系
those were sexual relationships.
没有爱的证据
There's no evidence of love.
嗯 当然没有爱的证据 罗伯特
Well, of course there's no evidence of love, Robert.
我们不被允许存在
We weren't allowed to exist.
我们怎么会有足够的证据？
How would we have enough evidence?
好吧 林肯和一个女人结婚 有四个孩子
Okay, Lincoln was married to a woman and had four children.
他不是同性恋 鲍比
He was not gay, Bobby.
他可能是双性恋
He might have been bi.
我告诉你
I am telling you!
我们已经让世界抹去了同性恋的爱情故事
We have let the world erase gay love stories
自古以来
since the beginning of time.
这是我们拒绝耻辱的机会
This is our chance to reject the shame
并恢复真相
and restore the truth.
如果我们不这样做 我们就会让他们赢
And if we don't do this, we're letting them win.
我们在让异性恋的恐怖分子获胜
We're letting the heterosexual terrorists win.
异性恋的恐怖分子？
The heterosexual terrorists?
是的  也有同性恋恐怖分子
That's right.  There are also gay terrorists.
也有双性恋恐怖分子 好吗？
And there are bi terrorists, okay?
有很多双性恋恐怖分子
There are many bisexual terrorists.
好吧 也有变性人恐怖分子
Okay, there are trans terrorists, too.
凯特琳·詹纳
Caitlyn Jenner.
够了 大家 我们来投票吧
Enough, people. Let's vote on it.
好的
Okay.
看来我们有两票
Looks like we have two votes
为世界伟大的双性恋者
for The Great Bisexuals of the World.
谢谢你 某人
Thank you, someone.
还有三票投给《林肯的信》
And three votes for The Lincoln Letters.
林肯获胜  是的!
Lincoln wins.  Yes!
谢谢你！谢谢你
Thank you! Thank you.
黛博拉·梅辛来了
Debra Messing is in the building.
我的姑娘
Yes! My girl.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
黛博拉·梅辛
Yeah.  Debra Messing.
是的 是的 是的 我很好
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
好的 祝我好运吧
Okay. Wish me luck.
梅辛小姐  哦 请叫我黛博拉
Miss Messing.  Oh, please call me Debra.
哦  哦
Oh.  Oh.
我喜欢这个地方
I love this space.
你是怎么找到它的？
How did you find it?
噢 我的天 我们是怎么找到它的？
Oh, God. How did we find it?
嗯 我不知道 我很抱歉
Um, I don't know. I'm sorry.
你还好吗 亲爱的？你看起来有点慌乱
Are you okay, dear? You seem a little flustered.
相信我
Trust me.
我知道我是黛博拉·梅辛 但我也只是个普通人
I know I'm Debra Messing, but I'm only human.
对
Right.
嗯 不 我很好
Um, no, I'm fine.
... 我很抱歉 是恋爱上的事情
It's a  I'm so sorry. It's boy problems.
这没什么 挺愚蠢的
It's nothing. It's stupid.
哦  是的
Oh.  Yeah.
事实上 他昨晚就在这里
He was actually here last night.
他和我一起去了筹款会
He came to the fundraiser with me
然后不知去哪了 他离开了 你知道吗
and then out of nowhere, he left, you know.
我一直给他发短信 他也不回我短信
And I keep texting him, and he doesn't text me back.
我不知道 这并不重要
I don't know. It doesn't matter.
你好吗？ 我对这次旅行非常兴奋
How are you?  I am so excited for this tour.
我可以很快的问你一句吗？
Can I just ask you really quickly?
因为我实际上认为
Because I actually think
你是最适合问的人
you're, like, the perfect person to ask.
发生了什么事？
What is going on?
你知道 比如 他对我不感兴趣
You know, like, is he not interested in me
还是真的出了什么事？
or did something really come up?
而我为什么要想这么多呢？
And why am I thinking about it so much?
这就是如此令人烦恼的原因
That's what's so annoying.
你知道 因为我从来没有像这样分心过 好吗？
You know, because I'm never distracted like this, okay?
这不是我的风格
This is not who I am.
这就像 我现在该怎么做？
And it's like, what do I do now?
我再给他发短信吗？我给他打电话吗？
Do I text him again? Do I call him?
我要去他家吗 你知道吗？
Do I go to his house, you know?
我该怎么做 黛博拉？
What do I do, Debra?
你知道 在过去的25年里
You know, for the last 25 years
我一直在听地球上所有的同性恋男人
I have been listening to every gay man on earth
向我抱怨
complain to me.
我不适合做自己
I am not my character.
我不是每个同性恋的最好朋友
I am not every gay man's best friend.
我只是在外面的世界上
I am simply out in the world
以为我会得到一个博物馆的参观机会 但是没有 没有！没有
thinking that I'm gonna get a tour of a museum, but no. No!
我有没有跳着华尔兹来到这里 向你吐槽我的屁事？
Did I waltz in here and lay all my shit on you?
回答我！回答我！ 我只是... ...  我...
Answer me! Answer me!  I'm just  I...
闭嘴！
Shut up!
我是一个离婚的单身母亲
I am a divorced single mother.
你想听听那是什么感觉吗？
You want to hear what that's like?
我对这件事很抱歉 我非常的尴尬
I'm so sorry about this. I'm terribly embarrassed.
请让我 让我重新开始 I...
Please let me, let me start again. I...
嘿 哇 哇 哇 这里发生了什么事？
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wh What's going on in here?
你们是否也有一些个人屁事
Do you have some personal shit
想向我抱怨什么？
you want to complain to me about?
没有   当然没有
No.  Of course not.
因为女同性恋只会默默承受一切
Because lesbians have their shit together.
我得走了 一小时后我的保姆就走了
I got to go. I lose my sitter in an hour.
梅辛小姐 请回来 我真的很抱歉
Miss Messing, please come back. I'm so sorry.
我不是格蕾丝！
I am not Grace!
这是个角色
It is a character.
我为此赢得了艾美奖
I won an Emmy for it.
我甚至打败了莎拉 杰西卡 帕克
I even beat Sarah Jessica Parker.
人们忘记了!
People forget!
我剃光头了
I'm shaving my head.
这他妈的是在这里做什么？
What the fuck is this doing here?
鲍比！你这是怎么了？
Bobby! What is going on with you?
黛博拉·梅辛刚刚让你滚蛋了
Debra Messing just told you to fuck off.
门他妈的锁着呢
The door's fucking locked.
哦 请让我帮你  不 我想要她
Oh, please let me help you.  No. I want her.
不要给他打电话
♪ Don't call him ♪
不要给他打电话 不要给他打电话
♪ Don't call him, don't call him ♪
不要给他打电话
♪ Do not call him ♪
只要看着奥扎克
♪ Just watch Ozark ♪
Ozark 就像一个正常人一样
♪ Ozark, like a normal person. ♪
嘿 是我
Hey, it's me.
嗯 听到请回电
Um, call me when you're around.
好的 再见
Okay, bye.
嘿 怎么了？
Hey, what's up?
什么事？
What's up?
对不起 我还没有回复
Sorry I haven't replied.
我只是一直很忙
I've just been busy.
不用担心 我也一样
No worries. Same.
这个周末你想出去玩吗？
You want to hang out this weekend?
嘿 鲍比 我必须说实话
Hey, Bobby. I have to be honest.
我真的很喜欢和你出去玩
I really like hanging out with you.
你是如此的聪明和有趣
You're so smart and funny
但我不确定我是否适合你
but I'm not sure I'm the right match for you.
我不确定我是否达到了你的水平
I'm not sure I'm at your level.
也许你的朋友说我很无聊是对的
Maybe your friends were right when they said I was boring.
祝你一切顺利
Good luck with everything.
哦 来吧
Oh, come on.
当然
Sure.
你为什么坐在草地上
Why are you sitting on the grass
而不是这张巨大的毯子？
and not this gigantic blanket?
我喜欢草地
I like grass.
嗯 酷 很好
Mm. Cool. Cool.
那么 有什么事吗？
So what's up?
最近发生了什么事？ 哦 等等
What's been going on?  Oh, wait.
疯狂的故事
Crazy story.
还记得我遇到的那个人吗？
Remember that guy I ran into
那个高中时的老同学？
that old buddy from high school?
是的  是的 他刚出柜了
Yeah.  Yeah. He just came out.
什么？
What?
和他的未婚妻分手了 我不知道
Broke up with his fiancée. I had no idea.
哇哦  疯了
Wow.  Crazy.
对他来说是好事  是啊
Good for him.  Yeah.
那很好
That's cool.
非常酷
Very cool.
好吧 抱歉 发生什么事了？
Okay, I'm sorry. What is going on?
什么意思？ 那天晚上
What do you mean?  The other night.
就那样把我丢在博物馆里
Leaving me at the museum like that.
然后你也没有回我的任何短信
And then you didn't return any of my texts.
嗯 你给我发了大概15条短信
Well, you texted me like 15 times.
这有点吓人
It was a little scary.
好吧 我需要你对我说实话
Okay, I need you to be honest with me.
我对你没有吸引力 对吗？
You're not attracted to me, right?
没关系的 我可以接受
It's okay. I can handle it.
我不会被侮辱的
I won't be insulted.
我只是需要知道
I just need to know.
只要你对我说实话 我就不会浪费我的时间
Just be honest with me so I don't waste my time.
我不是你喜欢的类型 对吗？ 鲍比 不是那样的
I'm not your type, right?  Bobby, it's not that.
你是个很有魅力的人  好吧 好吧 谢谢
You are a very attractive guy.  Okay. Well, thanks.
那么 你为什么要这么奇怪 这么消极怠工？
So why are you being so weird and passive aggressive?
听着 你的声音很大 实际上
Look, you're being very loud, actually.
你喜欢笨家伙  什么？
You like dumb guys.  What?
是的 你听到我说的了 我知道你喜欢什么了
Yeah, you heard me. I see what you like.
你喜欢这些大块头 像 他妈的兄弟
You like these big, like, fucking bro ey
就像 这些类固醇白痴
like, meathead idiots.
哦 这就是你喜欢的 亚伦？是吗？
Oh, is that what you like, Aaron? Yeah?
你想和大男孩一起玩 嗯？ 是的
You want to play with the big boys, huh?  Yep.
哦 看 艾伦 他们在打架
Oh, look, Aaron, they're fighting.
你想参加战斗？ 是的 没错
You want to be in the fight?  Yeah, that's right.
你想回到以前的高中更衣室里 嗯？
You want to be back in the old high school locker room, huh?
是的  和你的曲棍球朋友一起
Yeah.  With your hockey friends
就像 偷看他妈的乔希 对吗？
like, stealing a glance at fucking Josh, right?
嗯？是的 你喜欢这样吗？ 好的
Huh? Yeah, you like that?  Okay.
嘿
Hey.
是的 我可以很强硬  哦 哇
Yeah, I can be tough.  Oh, wow.
是的 我可以像你的男孩一样强硬
Yeah, I can be tough like your boys.
你别这样  是的 哦 这就是你喜欢的 嗯？
You stop that.  Yeah. Oh, that's what you like, huh?
哦 现在你在我的毯子上了 兄弟  是的 好的
Oh, now you're on my blanket, bro.  Yeah, okay.
是的 到我的毯子上 兄弟
Yeah, get on my blanket, bro.
哦 现在我在你的毯子上了  哦 现在你想
Oh, now I'm on your blanket.  Oh, now you want
在我的大毯子上？ 是的
on my big blanket?  Yeah.
现在你想在我的大毯子上？
Now you want to be on my big blanket?
我可以主动出击 哦 就是这样
I can be aggressive. Oh, there you are.
这样  我可以... 是吗？是啊 是啊？
There you  I can...  Yeah? Yeah, yeah?
嘿 嘿 嘿！发生什么事了？
Hey, hey, hey! What's going on?
我都在你的毯子上了  是吗？
I'm all over your blanket.  Yeah?
孩子们？
Boys?
好的 伙计  哦 是的  我的错
Okay, man.  Oh, yeah.  My bad.
我的地方就在这附近  让我们他妈的回家吧
My place is near here.  Let's go the fuck home.
是啊
Yeah.
嗷！嗷 哦 嗷！
Ow! Ow. Oh, ow!
嗷 嗷 嗷  当我坠入爱河
Ow, ow, ow.  ♪ When I fall in love ♪
哦 哇 哇！
Oh. Whoa, whoa!
嗷！哦
Ow! Oh.
这将是永远...
♪ It will be forever... ♪
是的  是的 我喜欢这样
Yeah.  Yeah. I like that.
我喜欢这样  你喜欢这样吗？
I like that.  You like that?
我喜欢那样  你要拿那个？
I like that.  You're gonna take that?
是的 这就是你喜欢的
Yeah, that's what you like.
哦 是的
Ooh, yeah.
哦 是的 肮脏 哦 是的
Oh, yeah. Dirty. Oh, yeah.
哦 是的
Oh, yeah.
哦 是的  哦 是吗？是吗？
Oh, yeah.  Oh, yeah? Yeah?
嗯哼
Uh huh.
嗯 嗯 你喜欢这个吗？ 是的 是的
Mm hmm. You like that?  Yeah. Yes.
嗯哼 嗯哼  是的 好的
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.  Yeah. Okay.
嗯哼 是的 嗯 嗯
Mm hmm. Yeah.  Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
是的 好的
Yeah. Okay.
好吗？是吗？
Good? Yeah?  Mm hmm.
哦 是的 哦 是吗？
Ooh, yeah. Oh, yeah?
你要拍垫认输吗？ 是的 是的 我会认输的
You gonna tap out?  Yeah, yeah, I'll tap out.
是吗？哦 是的 是吗？
Yeah? Oh, yeah. Yeah?  I'll tap out.
你要认输吗？我认输  我认输
You gonna tap out? Tap out.  I'll tap out.
我认输好吗！ 你还好吗？你行吗？
I tap out!  Are you good? Are you good?
我要认输 我要认输 好吧 我很抱歉 好的
I tapped out. I tapped out.  Okay, I'm sorry. Okay.
哦
Oh.
哦 哦
Oh! Oh.
很好 是的 你喜欢这个吗？ 嗯哼 嗯哼
Great. Yeah, you like that?  Uh huh. Uh huh.
是的 你喜欢吗？是的 你喜欢吗？
Yeah, you like that? Yeah, you like that?
哦 是的 哦 是的 是的 是的 你喜欢吗？你喜欢吗？
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah.  You like that? You like that?
哦 是的 你喜欢这样吗？ 是的 是的 是的
Oh, yeah. You like that?  Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
是啊！是的！ Yeah. 是的
Yeah! Yeah!  Yeah. Yeah.
你想吸rush吗？
You like poppers?
可以
Yeah.  Okay.
我的心
♪ My heart ♪
那一刻
♪ And the moment ♪
我可以感觉到
♪ I can feel that ♪
你也有这种感觉
♪ You feel that way, too ♪
就是我爱上你的时候
♪ Is when I fall in love ♪
和你在一起
♪ With you. ♪
这很疯狂
That was crazy.
是啊
Yeah.
我喜欢你的胸部像这样陷下去
I like how your chest goes in like that.
哦 谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
嗯 这就是所谓的凹陷的胸部
Mm, it's called a concave chest.
嗯 我喜欢它
Well, I like it.
这就像一个小鸟巢
It's like a tiny birdbath.
就像一个鸟巢？
It's like a birdbath?
嗯  很好
Mm.  Great.
我一直希望我的胸部
I always wanted my chest
看起来就像一个小鸟巢
to look exactly like a tiny birdbath.
这是每一个男人都想要的
It's what every man wants.
我喜欢你的毛茸茸的样子
I like how hairy you are.
你就像奥斯汀·鲍尔斯
You're like Austin Powers.
谢谢你
Thank you.
天啊 我从来没有想过我会和一个比黛布拉·梅辛
God, I never thought I would date someone who gets
更喜欢奥斯汀·鲍尔斯的人约会
more excited about Austin Powers than Debra Messing.
我哪里做错了？
Where did I go wrong?
等等 我们在约会吗？
Wait. Are are we dating?
没有
No.
我们没有约会 好吧
We're not dating. Please.
我是在开玩笑
I was joking.
你不和人约会 我不和人约会
You don't date people. I don't date people.
我们不和人约会
We don't date people.
记得吗？ 我记得
Remember?  I remember.
嗷 你在做什么？
Ow. What are you doing?
温暖的身体感觉如此之好 真是令人讨厌
So annoying how good a warm body feels
躺在另一个温暖的身体上
laying on another warm body.
嗯？ 我讨厌在星期天收到工作邮件
Hmm?  I hate getting work emails on a Sunday.
你的工作真的很紧张
Your job is really intense.
是的 我讨厌它
Yes, and I hate it.
它他妈的压力很大 很压抑
It's fucking stressful and depressing
而且太他妈的无聊了 我...
and so fucking boring. I I...
我他妈的讨厌它
I fucking hate it.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你还有别的事要做吗？
Was there something else you wanted to do?
鲍比 我需要告诉你一些事情
Bobby, I need to tell you something.
当我年轻的时候...
When I was younger...
发生了什么事？ I...
What happened?  I...
你可以告诉我
You can tell me.
当我年轻的时候 我想做小巧克力
When I was younger, I wanted to make little chocolates.
你想做...
You wanted to make...
小巧克力？ 是的
little chocolates?  Yes.
我曾经告诉我的父母我要去商场的电玩城
I used to tell my parents I was going to the arcade
但我还是会偷偷跑到歌帝梵去
at the mall, but I would sneak off to Godiva.
我只是喜欢所有巧克力的包装方式
I just loved how all the chocolates were wrapped.
我想过我将如何设计我自己的巧克力
And I thought about how I would design my own chocolates
每个小巧克力都有
how each little chocolate has
都有自己特定的、独特的设计
its own specific, unique design on it
而这个小设计告诉你
and that little design tells you
它们会是什么味道的
what they're gonna taste like.
所以我会在记事本上画我自己的巧克力
So I would draw my own chocolates in in a notepad.
这就是我所想的
It's all I thought about.
小小的漂亮巧克力
Tiny little pretty chocolates.
这很好
That's good.
但这样又能做些什么呢？
What was I gonna do with that, though?
我又能成为什么呢？
What was I gonna be?
巧克力师？
A chocolatier?
鲍比 我才不会去成为该死的巧克力师
Bobby, I wasn't gonna be a fucking chocolatier.
我不知道 为什么不呢？
I don't know. Why not?
它似乎有点娘娘腔
It seemed kind of faggy.
噢 我的天 亚伦
Oh, my God, Aaron.
娘娘腔？
Faggy?
制作漂亮的小巧克力
It's not faggy to spend your life
并没有很娘娘腔
making pretty little chocolates.
鲍比  好吧 好吧
Bobby.  Okay, fine.
但那又怎样？所以你是个死同性恋
But so what? So you're a big fag.
我也是 这很好
So am I. It's great.
你难道没有意识到 几分钟前
Did you not realize that a few minutes ago
你把大鸡巴
when you were sticking your enormous penis
插入我的小穴？ 好吧 是的
into my tiny anus?  Okay, yeah.
这是一种陈词滥调 你不觉得吗？
It It's kind of cliché, don't you think?
我宁愿成为俗套的人 也不愿成为一个悲惨的人
I'd rather be a cliché than be miserable.
嗯 我15岁的大脑在1995年
Well, my 15 year old brain in 1995
这就是我所想的
that is all I thought about.
就在那段时间里
That was right around the time
我的哥哥发现了
that my brother caught me.
发现你和男人勾搭在一起？ 没有
Hooking up with a guy?  No.
不 发现我在做小巧克力
No, I was making little chocolates.
哦
Oh.
我撒谎了 我说我在... ...
I lied, and I said that I was...
为某位学校里暗恋的
making chocolates for this girl
女孩做巧克力
that I had a crush on at school.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这是我听过的最可爱的事情
This is the cutest thing I've ever heard.
我猜你只是有这庞大的 令人兴奋的生活
I guess you just have this big, exciting life.
我只是不想让你认为我是个无聊的笨蛋
I just didn't want you to think that I was some boring schlub.
我不认为你很无聊
I don't think you're boring.
你的朋友说我很无聊
Your friend said I was boring.
噢 我的天 你为这个生气了？
Oh, my God. You were mad about that?
我是在开玩笑 我很抱歉
I was joking. I'm sorry.
但是 我不明白
But, like, I don't understand.
你没必要整天呆在那个悲惨的办公室里
You don't have to be stuck in that miserable office all day.
你可以到外面的世界 我不知道
You could be out in the world, I don't know
制作软糖 你知道吗？
making fudge, you know?
你就像一个内在恐同的饼干小精灵
You're like a Keebler elf with internalized homophobia.
你必须这样做
You have to do this.
你必须成为一个巧克力师
You have to become a chocolatier.
哦 鲍比  你必须成为一个巧克力师
Oh, Bobby.  You have to become a chocolatier.
我告诉你
I'm telling you.
你让这听起来很容易
You make that sound so easy.
嗯 不 这不容易
Well, no, it's not easy.
没有什么是容易的
Nothing's easy.
我的天 你知道我这个周末要做什么吗？
My God. You know what I have to do this weekend?
我必须拖着我的凹陷的胸部
I have to drag my concave chest
到普罗旺斯镇 向捐赠者乞讨资金
up to Provincetown and beg donors for money.
我需要500万美元 否则博物馆就不能开放
I need $5 million or else the museum can't open.
而且那里是骄傲节 所以博物馆必须要有
And it's Pride up there, so the museum has to have
花车参加游行 这是个大问题
a float in the parade, and that's a whole thing.
我告诉你 这并不容易
I'm telling you, it is not easy.
从来都不容易
It is never easy.
但这是值得的
But it's worth it.
嘿 也许我可以来
Hey, maybe I can come.
去哪里？
To where?
普罗旺斯镇？
Provincetown?
哦
Oh.
是的
Yeah.
来吧 来吧 来吧 欢迎 我是路易斯
Come, come, come. Welcome. I'm Louis.
让我带你看看你的卧室
Let me show you your bedroom.
谢谢你 噢 我的天
Thank you. Oh, my God.
这房子太漂亮了  哦
This house is so beautiful.  Oh.
你有这个地方多久了？
How long have you had this place?
哦 我1976年就在普罗旺斯镇了
Oh, I've been coming up to P town since, uh, 1976.
哇哦  这些人都是谁？
Wow.  Who are all these guys?
哦 嗯 事实上 那是我
Oh, well, um, actually, that's me.
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
路易斯 你太性感了
Louis, you were so hot.
是的 我知道  哇哦
Yeah, I know.  Wow.
这些人中有谁还会来这里吗？
Do any of these guys still come up here, too?
呃 没有
Uh, no.
到了1996年 他们七个人中有四个人已经走了
By 1996, four of the seven of them were gone.
我在1999年得到了这个地方 当时我意识到 以某种方式
I got this place in 1999 when I realized that somehow
我将奇迹般地 活下来
miraculously, I was gonna survive.
哦 我很抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry.
那么 告诉我 你们这些人今天有什么事吗？
So, tell me. What are you boys up to today?
哦 好吧 我今天下午有一个工作的事情
Oh, well, I have a work thing this afternoon
所以我真的不知道
so I don't really know.
可能只是低调行事  低调行事？
Probably just lay low.  Lay low?
你在普罗旺斯镇
You're in P town.
出去吧 玩得开心点
Go out. Have fun.
人也活不了多长时间 去吧
You'll be dead soon enough. Come on.
让我带你们到房间  好的
Let me show you to your room.  All right.
这是你们的卧室
Here's your bedroom.
噢 我的天
Oh, my God!
哦 哇
Oh, wow.
如果你想做爱 请让我知道
And if you want to fuck, you let me know.
哦 嗯  嗯   嗯
Oh. Mm.  Mm.
嘿 我得去拿点东西 哦 该死
Hey, I need to grab something. Oh, shit.
鲍比  我很抱歉
Bobby.  I'm sorry.
为什么你就这么走了进来？
Why are you just walking in here?
我很抱歉 我以为你在洗澡
I'm sorry. I thought you were in the shower.
这不是类固醇 这只是睾丸激素
It's not steroids. It's just testosterone.
这不是很危险吗 比如
Isn't that dangerous, like
对于你的肝脏和睾丸之类的？
for your liver and balls and stuff?
不 我认识的一半的人都在用这东西
No. Half the guys I know do this stuff.
是的 但你认识的一半人都是类固醇白痴
Yeah, but half the guys you know are roided out morons.
是的 好吧 这似乎并不妨碍你
Yeah, well, that doesn't seem to bother you
当你迷恋上我的身体的时候
when you're obsessing over my body.
好吧 这很公平
Okay, that's fair.
嗯 我要去洗澡
Um, I'm gonna shower.
她把我的心
♪ She's taken my heart ♪
但她不知道她做了什么
♪ But she doesn't know what she's done ♪
我觉得她的呼吸在我的脸上
♪ I feel her breath in my face ♪
她的身体紧贴着我
♪ Her body close to me ♪
不能看她的眼睛
♪ Can't look in her eyes ♪
她是在我的范围之外
♪ She's out of my league ♪
只是一个傻瓜 相信我有任何她需要的东西
♪ Just a fool to believe I have anything she needs ♪
她就像风
♪ She's like the wind. ♪
你的声音真好听
You have a really nice voice.
什么？
What?
我听到你在洗澡时唱歌
I heard you singing in the shower.
嗯 挺羞愧的
Well, that's mortifying.
等等 所以你要求这个人捐出
Wait, so you're asking this guy to donate
剩下的五百万？
the remaining five million?
不 要是我可以从他那里得到一百万 也是能接受的
No. If I can get one million out of him, I'll take it.
你不能因为看起来太需要就把这些人吓跑了
You can't scare these people off by seeming too needy.
有点像对你
Kind of like with you.
谁是 劳伦斯·格拉普？
Who's Lawrence Grape?  Larry Grape.
这个星球上最大的同性恋电视制作人
Biggest gay TV producer on the planet.
他制作了所有这些突破性的同性恋内容
He's made all this groundbreaking queer content.
他是个大人物
He's major.
格拉普先生 我在想
Mr. Grape, I'm thinking
最后一翼应该是关于林肯的
the final wing should be about Lincoln.
喜欢 喜欢林肯
Love that. Love Lincoln.
很少有人知道这一点
Very few people know this
但我们最受欢迎的总统
but our most popular president
也是我们的第一位同性恋总统
was also our first gay president.
对不起 这是一个林肯博物馆？
Sorry. This is a Lincoln museum?
这是一个林肯博物馆吗 先生？
Is this a Lincoln museum, sir?
这实际上是一个LGBTQ历史博物馆
This is actually an LGBTQ history museum.
这是在全国范围内的第一个此类博物馆
It's the first of its kind on a national level.
我们实际上...
We actually s...
那个该死的灌木丛！
That fucking bush! Come on.
我的邻居种了那片灌木 它挡住了我的视线
My neighbors planted that bush, and it blocks my view.
你能相信吗？
Can you believe that?
我们去处理一下这个
Let's go take care of this.
哦 又是这个？你在做什么？
Oh, again with this? What are you doing?
这是在我的财产上 莫里斯！
This is on my property, Maurice!
这是共同的边界线！
This is a shared borderline!
这真他妈是个灾难 他甚至不听我的话
This is a fucking disaster. He won't even listen to me.
他忙着让他的罗威纳犬准备好迎接骄傲行
He's too busy getting his rottweiler ready for Pride.
好吧 根据我的工作经验
Okay, from my experience at my job
怪异的富人只想被倾听
weird rich people just want to be listened to.
问他对什么感兴趣
Ask him what he's interested in.
但我并不关心他对什么感兴趣
But I don't care what he's interested in.
我是来向他介绍我的想法的
I'm here to pitch him my idea.
好吧 那就装作你感兴趣的样子
Well, then pretend like you're interested.
就做个倾听的表情
Just do a listening face.
做一个倾听的表情？ 是的
Do a listening face?  Yeah.
嗯 是的
Hmm. Yeah.
我不能  是的 来吧 去吧
I can't.  Yes. Come on. Go.
好的
Okay.
是的 是的 这很好  真的吗？
Yes. Yeah, that's good.  Really?
那看起来像我在听？
That looked like I'm listening?
当然 是的   哦
Totally. Yeah.  Oh.
...把这个种在我的土地上！
...plant this on my property!
这是一种当地的灌木！ 你要去 "骄傲游行 "吗？
It's an indigenous bush!  Are you going to Pride?
当然了  我会在那里见到你
Of course.  I'll see you there.
爱你  哦 我也爱你
Love you.  Oh, I love you, too.
好的 听着 我试试吧 我试试吧
All right. Listening. I'll try it. I'll try it.
对不起 我得走了 伙计们
Sorry. I have to get going, boys.
哦 格拉普先生 让我问你一件事
Oh, Mr. Grape, let me ask you something.
嗯...
Um...
你想在博物馆里看到什么？
what would you like to see in the museum?
一座闹鬼的房子
A haunted house
同性恋创伤的鬼屋
of gay trauma.
同性恋创伤的鬼屋？
A haunted house of gay trauma?
是的 一条轨道上的小车 还有...
Yeah. It's a cart on a track, and there's...
我很抱歉 这是个游乐设施？
I'm sorry. This is a ride?
是的 这是个该死的游乐设施！
Yeah, it's a fucking ride!
所以你觉得坐车太过分了？
So you think a ride is too much?
嗯 不 不  不
Um, no. N No.
不 不 不 不 这很完美 拜托 继续说
No, no, no, no. It's perfect. Please, keep going.
好的 我们发现自己在
Okay. We find ourselves in
亲密的小酒吧 和一些年轻的
an intimate little bar with some young
热情洋溢的动画般的人
hot, animatronic men.
这些人转过身来和对方跳舞 突然...... "砰！"
The men turn to dance with each other when suddenly  Boom!
哦 我的...
Oh, my...
一辆警车撞破了墙
A cop car smashes through the wall.
警察从车里冲出来
Police storm out of the cars.
警笛声、警棍声和尖叫声此起彼伏
There's sirens and batons and voices screaming.
突然 汽车像过山车一样起飞了
And suddenly, the car takes off like a roller coaster
而且到处都是血
and there's blood everywhere.
一个印有里根脸的怪物在走廊上追着你说
And a monster with Reagan's face on it is chasing you
说 "山巅上的光辉之城
down the hallway saying, "Shining city on a hill.
山巅上的光辉之城 "
Shining city on a hill."
然后......我们射向光明
And then... we shoot out into the light.
然后在一些快乐的事情上结束
And it ends on something happy
就好像李娜叉用粉色哑铃锻炼
like Lil Nas X working out with pink dumbbells.
哇
Wow.
嗯 同性恋的创伤过山车
Um, a gay trauma coaster.
我的意思是 它... 它非常具有挑衅性
I I mean, it's it's very provocative.
我只是不认为我们能负担得起
I just don't think we can afford
那种东西 不幸的是
that sort of thing, unfortunately.
对 好吧 好吧 很高兴见到你 G...
Right. Well, okay, it was so lovely meeting you g...
格拉普先生
Mr. Grape, Mr. Grape.
我不是一个有创造力的人 我只是个赚钱的家伙
I'm not a creative guy. I'm a money guy.
不 不 不 不 不 不   我  不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no.  I  No, no.
我可以告诉你 要完成你想要的东西
I can tell you, to accomplish what you want
我们需要的不仅仅是一笔小小的捐款
we need more than just a little donation.
不 亚伦...  我们需要500万美金
No, Aaron...  We need $5 million.
而且你不会只得到同性恋的创伤过山车
And you won't just get the gay trauma coaster.
你会得到林肯展览 你会得到所有的东西
You get the Lincoln exhibit. You get all of it.
你为整个LGBTQ社区改写历史
You rewrite history for an entire LGBTQ community.
你是一个讲故事的人 劳伦斯 而这是一个终极故事
You're a storyteller, Lawrence, and this is the ultimate story.
你已经把博物馆的开放时间推后了两次
You already pushed the museum opening back twice.
它真的要发生了吗？
Is it really happening?
是的！它肯定会发生 我保证
Yes! It's definitely happening. I promise.
我是为这个而生的
My entire life has led up to this.
好吧 500万美元来改写历史
Right, well, $5 million is nothing
不算什么
to rewrite history.
我加入了
I'm in.
等等 真的吗？
Wait, really?
好啊  我的天 格拉普先生 谢谢你！
Yes! Yes!  Oh, my God! Mr. Grape, thank you!
当然了
Of course.
用钱愉快 骄傲行快乐
Congratulations on my money. Happy Pride.
骄傲行 现在我必须要去
Happy Pride!  Now I have to go
去参加一个骄傲派对 而你们两个都太老了 不能去舞池
to a Pride party, and you're both too old to be in the pool.
请离开
Please leave.
亚伦！我的天
Aaron! Oh, my God!
你真是个天才
You're a genius.
"你是个讲故事的人"？
"You're a storyteller"?
这句话到底是怎么来的？ 我告诉过你
Where did that even come from?  I told you.
我很擅长和古怪的富人交谈
I'm good at talking to weird rich folk.
我看得出他有钱可花
I could tell he had money to spend.
我 我不知道该说什么
I I don't know what to say.
谢谢你
Thank you.
当然
Sure.
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
哦 该死！我得去参加游行了
Oh, shit! I got to go to the parade.
我得去坐那辆愚蠢的花车了
I got to get on that stupid float.
我们之后见  好的
I'll see you after.  Okay.
好的 谢谢你
Okay. Thank you.
好的
Okay.
我吻了你！
I kissed you!
我们现在是可以亲吻对方了吗？我不知道！再见！
Are we kissing each other now? I don't know! Bye!
鲍比！
Bobby!
你真漂亮
You're gorgeous.
什么 你是
What? You are.
我仍然无法相信你今天对劳伦斯所做的一切
I still can't believe what you did with Lawrence today.
这真是太不可思议了!
That was amazing!
五百万美元？
$5 million?
这不是什么大交易
It's not that big a deal.
这是一个巨大的交易 你在跟我开玩笑吗？
It is a huge deal. Are you kidding me?
我总是要为自己做一切
I always have to do everything for myself.
从来没有人为我做过这样的事情
No one ever does shit like that for me.
你知道 你为我做的事 你可以为自己做
You know, what you did for me you could do for yourself.
开一家巧克力店 我不知道
Open a chocolate shop. I don't know.
我不会开一家巧克力店
I'm not opening a chocolate shop.
我不像你那么自信
I'm not as confident as you.
哦 拜托 我没那么自信
Oh, please. I'm not that confident.
你是我认识的最自信的人
You are the most confident person I know
就像 到了一定的程度
like, to a fault.
这实际上...
It's actually
这有点吓人
It's kind of scary.
相信我 这都是装出来的
Trust me, it's all an act.
自信只是你的一个选择
Confidence is just a choice you make.
和其他任何决定一样
It's a decision like any other.
通常是在必要的情况下产生的
Usually born out of necessity.
你认为我现在有一副好歌喉？
You think I have a good singing voice now?
你应该听听我小时候的声音
You should have heard me when I was a kid.
我当时甚至更好
I was even better.
如果那时有《美国偶像》的存在
Had American Idol existed then
我就会是那个拥有惊人嗓音的同性恋
I would've been the gay guy with an amazing voice
排名第二
who comes in second.
然后让我想想
And then let's see.
然后我上了大学 我的音乐剧老师
Then I went to college, and my musical theater teacher
他告诉我 走路太同性恋了
he told me that I had a "gay walk"
以及 "浮夸的品质" 这将 "限制我的选择"
and a "flamboyant quality" which would "limit my options."
然后在研究生院 我去了
And then for grad school, I went to
全国最好的新闻学院之一
one of the best journalism schools in the country
而我在那里的老师
and my teacher there
一位年老深柜的同性恋 娶了一个女人
this old, closeted queen who was married to a woman
把我置之一边  认为是在帮我的忙
pulled me aside and thought he was doing me a favor
他告诉我 我应该坚持写作
when he told me that I should stick to writing
因为我的声音听起来太同性恋了 不能在电视上做新闻
because my voice sounded too gay to do the news on TV.
这是一个真实的故事
True story.
然后 我确实坚持写作和我的同性恋历史书籍
And then I did stick to writing and my gay history books.
每一个出版商 每一个人
Every single publisher, every single one
都告诉我没有足够的读者
told me there wasn't enough of an audience for it.
我总是太同性恋 或者我太小众
I was always too gay, or I was too niche
或者 你知道 我让人们感到不舒服
or, you know, I made people uncomfortable.
即使是我的父亲 他是如此支持我.. ...
Even my dad, who was so wonderful and supportive
我记得他说 "你知道 不是每个人
I remember him saying, "You know, not everyone
都想一直听这些同性恋的东西 "
wants to hear this gay stuff all the time."
但是我应该怎么做呢？
But what was I supposed to do?
我是说... 我是个作家
I mean... I'm a writer.
我想写我的生活 我的朋友 我的世界
I wanted to write about my life, my friends, my world.
而且我告诉你
And I'm telling you
足够多的人告诉你这样的事情
enough people tell you things like that
不管你有多自信
no matter how confident you are
当你在晚上独自一人时
when you're alone at night
你就会开始想 也许他们是对的
you start to think that maybe they're right.
所以...我只是...
So... I just...
默默低头
I put my head down
埋头苦干
and I just worked really hard
我只是希望 无论如何
and I just hoped that somehow
这些人都是错的
all these other people were wrong.
而他们确实错了
And they were.
他们确实错了
我的意思是 在这数年之间
I mean, I spent years
我目睹着一波波平庸之辈同我擦肩而过
watching a wave of mediocre straight men passing me by.
那些直男的天赋与勤奋，远不及我
Men with half the talent, who worked half as hard
甚至他们都不如我在意这些
who didn't care as much as I did
但他们抵达之处，我们望尘莫及
and they got twice as far, always.
我懂 这都是一些老生常谈 但...
I mean, that's an old story, but...
那个 你知道 世界追上了我们
And, you know, the world caught up with us.
但完全不够
Didn't catch up fast enough.
还不足让我的父母来亲眼见证
Didn't catch up fast enough for my parents to see
在我身上发生的所有这些美好之事
all these great things happen for me.
对吗？
Right?
对很多人来说 世界的速度还远不够快
Didn't catch up fast enough for a lot of people.
这就是事实
That's the truth.
让我告诉你 自信就是知道
Let me tell you, confidence is just knowing
你是你唯一可以依靠的人
you're the only person left you can count on.
这就是全部
That's all that is.
就是这样
That's all.
想再来一杯啤酒吗？
Want another beer?
当然
Sure.
对不起 有点过了
Sorry. That was a lot.
这让你感到奇怪吗？
Did that weird you out?
我想要的朋友  嗯 宝贝 爱
♪ The friends that I want ♪  ♪ Well, baby, love ♪
爱 哦哦哦
♪ Love, ooh ooh ♪
和朋友在一起 我还是觉得很没有安全感
♪ With friends, I still feel so insecure ♪
小宝贝 我相信你能帮助我很多
♪ Little darling, I believe you could help me a lot ♪
牵着我的手 带我到你想去的地方...
♪ Just take my hand and lead me where you will... ♪
我喜欢这首歌
I love this song.
好吧 宝贝 爱  爱 呜呜呜
♪ Well, baby, love ♪  ♪ Love, ooh ooh ♪
只要用感情去做爱
♪ Just make love with affection ♪
再给我唱一首情歌...
♪ Sing me another love song... ♪
你跳舞有点奇怪
That is a weird dance.
请原谅我
Excuse me.
至少我跳舞了
At least I dance.
我可以跳舞
I can dance.
我从未见过你跳舞 真的 没有人见过
I have never seen you dance. Literally, no one has.
真的吗？ 没有
Really?  No.
想看我跳舞吗？ 是的
Want to see me dance?  Yes.
呃 哦
Uh oh.
给我爱 给我爱...
♪ Give me love, give me love... ♪
哦 很好
Oh. Very good.
这就对了  来吧
There you go.  Come on.
我想让你干我
I want you to fuck me.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
你最后一次这样做是什么时候？
When was the last time you did that?
已经有一段时间了
It's been a while.
但我想让你做
But I want you to.
好的 很好
Okay.  Good.
但这次要有一点奉献精神
♪ But this time with a little dedication ♪
唱吧 唱吧 唱吧 唱吧
♪ Sing it, sing it, sing it, sing it ♪
你知道这是我喜欢的吗
♪ You know that's what I like ♪
爱  爱 呜呜呜
♪ Love ♪  ♪ Love, ooh ooh ♪
再一次有感而发
♪ Once more with feeling ♪
再给我唱一首情歌
♪ Sing me another love song ♪
但这一次...
♪ But this time... ♪
是的 好的 给你
Yeah. All right. Here you go.
圣诞快乐  谢谢你 圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.  Thank you. Merry Christmas.
谢谢你 圣诞快乐
Thank you. Merry Christmas.
好的
Okay.
哇哦 好了 准备好了吗？
Whoa. Okay.  Ready?
很好 很好
Great. Fine.
会很好的  呜呜
It's gonna be good.  Whew.
这一切都值得！ 是的
It's all worth it!  Yeah.
这一切都值得！
It's all worth it!
怎么了？亚伦！
What's up? Aaron!
什么...  怎么了 伙计？
Wh...  What's up, man?
哇哦  我还在想什么时候能碰上你呢
Whoa.  I was wondering when I was gonna run into you.
就好像七个我们一样
It's like seven of us.
嘿 恭喜你的一切
Hey, congratulations on everything.
是的 谢谢你 是的 这很疯狂 伙计
Yeah, thank you. Yeah, it's been crazy, man.
很好 那么 嗯 你一直在做什么？
Cool. So, um, yeah, what have you been doing?
路易斯说 "不 我需要看选项 "
Louis was like, "No, I need to see options."
然后他开始给我发Airbnb的选择
And then he started sending me Airbnb options.
我让你觉得无聊吗？ 不 不 不
Am I boring you?  No, no, no.
我就说 "不 我们值得这样..."
And I'm like, "No, we deserve this..."
鲍比
Bobby.
你想要什么？ 我想要你
What do you want?  I want you.
怎么了？
What's up?
嗯 我们在这个问题上的立场是什么？
Um, where do we stand on this?
我们在什么上的立场？
Where do we stand on what?
"Momogany"  噢
"Momogany."  Oh.
关于 "Momogany"？
On "momogany"?
我们是开放性关系吗？我们对什么感兴趣？我们在做什么呢？
Are we open? What are we into? What are we doing? Like...
哦 这就像《当哈利遇见莎莉》
Oh, this is just like When Harry Met Sally.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
这就是那个经典的场景 比利 克里斯托尔
It's that classic scene where Billy Crystal
在新年前夜跑到梅格 瑞恩面前 问她
runs to Meg Ryan on New Year's Eve and asks her
是否想要有一个开放式的关系
if she wants to have an open relationship.
好吧 但是... ...  我的意思是
Well, but...  I mean
我的意思是 我不喜欢 一夫一夫制 你知道
I'm not, like, into monogamy, you know.
但我不认为我们应该 比如
But I don't think we should be, like
不断地和别人上床
constantly fucking other people.
那肯定不
No.
你为什么这么问？
Why do you ask?
哦 你想操你的小曲棍球朋友
Oh, you want to fuck your little hockey friend.
不 我想操你
No, I want to fuck you.
哦 那很好  但也许他也在那里
Oh, that's nice.  But maybe he's there, too.
他很性感
He's very hot.
嗨 约书亚  嘿  嘿
Hi, Joshua.  Hey.  Hey.
嗨
Hi.
我是史蒂夫
I'm Steve.
嗨 史蒂夫  嗨 史蒂夫
Hey, Steve.  Hey, Steve.
嗨 史蒂夫
Hi, Steve.
圣诞老人宝贝
♪ Santa baby ♪
把貂皮放在树下
♪ Just slip a sable under the tree... ♪
嗨 史蒂夫
Hi, Steve.
嘿
Hey.
一直是一个可怕的好女孩...
♪ Been an awful good girl... ♪
所以今晚赶紧从烟囱下来
♪ So hurry down the chimney tonight ♪
圣诞老人宝贝
♪ Santa baby ♪
嗯
Mmm.
'54敞篷车 太 浅蓝色...
♪ A '54 convertible, too, light blue... ♪
哦 对不起
Oh, sorry.
嘿
Hey.
圣诞老人宝贝...
♪ Santa baby... ♪
枕头大战！
Pillow fight!
可以给我按摩一下吗？
Can I have a massage?
我？
Me?
想想所有的乐趣 我已经错过了...
♪ Think of all the fun I've missed... ♪
当然可以
Sure.
我的腿筋真的很紧
I got really tight hamstrings.
很好  哦 是的
Cool.  Oh, yeah.
就在那里
Right there.
如果你会检查了我的圣诞清单
♪ If you'll check off my Christmas list ♪
圣诞老人宝贝...
♪ Santa baby... ♪
别理我 我想我把我的围巾留在这里 我可以...
Ignore me. I think I left my scarf in here. I can...
亨利！滚出去！
Henry! Get out!
鲍比 莱伯！
Bobby Leiber!
你交了一些朋友
You made some friends.
嗨 亨利  嗨 史蒂夫
Hi, Henry.  Hey, Steve.
哦 当然
Oh, sure.
我宿醉得很厉害
I am so hungover.
嗯
Mm.
谢谢你
Thank you.
所以 我可能错了 关于
So, I may have been wrong about
勾搭别人的事
the whole hooking up with other people thing.
好吧
Okay.
我也不知道 我只是...
I don't know. I just...
我想变得很酷 很自由 而且 你知道
I want to be cool and free, and, you know
我不想看起来很差劲 但实际上看到你
I don't want to be lame, but actually seeing you
我不知道 它只是...
I don't know. It just...
这对我不管用
It wasn't working for me.
是的 不 完全 我明白了
Yeah, no, totally. I I get it.
你确定？
You sure?
是的
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
哦 对不起 我妈妈一直在给我发短信
Oh. Sorry, my mom will not stop texting me.
你的家人什么时候再到这里？
When do your folks get here again?
21号
The 21st.
她想做
She wants to do the whole
"在纽约过神奇的圣诞节 "的事情
"magical Christmas in New York" thing.
他们喜欢观光
They love sightseeing.
我不知道该和他们做什么
I have no idea what to do with them.
好吧 如果你需要我 我就在家里
Well, if you need me, I'll be home
讨厌看霍尔心的圣诞电影
hate watching Hallheart Christmas movies.
嘿
Hey.
你也许想跟我和我的家人一起过圣诞节？
Do you maybe want to spend Christmas with me and my folks?
真的吗？
Really?
因为 说实话 我一个人完全没问题
Because, honestly, I am totally fine alone.
不过 你真是太贴心了
That is very sweet of you, though.
不 你不应该独自一人 那太疯狂了
No, you shouldn't be alone. That's crazy.
好吧
Okay.
是啊 会很有趣的
Yeah, that'll be fun.
而且 说实话 没有人比我更了解纽约市
And, honestly, no one knows New York City better than me.
我将计划纽约市的终极圣诞节
I will plan the ultimate New York City Christmas
因为只有纽约市的犹太人才能做到
as only a New York City Jew could.
很好
Amazing.
但请记住 你知道
But just keep in mind, you know
他们是来自一个小镇的安静的人
they're, like, quiet folks from a small town.
亚伦 我理解
Aaron, I understand.
你和我来自不同的世界
You and I come from different worlds.
我来自纽约市 你来自纽约州北部
I'm from New York City. You're from Upstate New York.
我的意思是 他们是可爱的 但只是...
I mean, they're sweet, but just...
如果你能 比如说 放松一点
If you could just be, like, chill.
我保证我不会让你难堪
I promise I won't embarrass you.
而且 谢泼德夫人 这些是
And, Mrs. Shepard, these are the first holiday windows
有史以来第一个以性为主题的Tiny Tim为特色的节日橱窗
to ever feature a sex positive Tiny Tim.
这很重要
And it's so important.
在我们小时候读的故事中
We don't get queer characters
我们没有酷儿角色
in the stories that we read as kids.
没有男同灰姑娘
There's no gay Cinderella.
没有女同长发公主
There's no lesbian Rapunzel.
没有非二元化的埃比尼泽 斯库吉（狄更斯的《圣诞颂歌》中的人物）
There's no nonbinary Ebenezer Scrooge.
呃 鲍比 我想他们明白了
Uh, Bobby, I think they get it.
伙计们 我们得走了
Guys, we've got to go.
我告诉乔什 埃文斯我们会在
I told Josh Evans we would meet him
在Hallheart圣诞电影快闪式村庄见
at the Hallheart Christmas movie pop up village.
我们要见乔什 埃文斯？
We're seeing Josh Evans?
我不知道
I didn't know.
让我们开始吧
Let's do it.
你是Hallheart的粉丝吗？
Are you a Hallheart fan?
我涉足过一点
I dabble.
这真是太美了
This is so beautiful.
我知道 我喜欢它
I know. I love it.
那是乔希
There's Josh.
在冬天穿短裤 像个十足的神经病
Wearing shorts in winter, like a total psychopath.
哦 我的天哪
Oh, my goodness.
他们有Rachael Ray可食用的锡纸！
They have Rachael Ray edible tinsel!
乔希！埃文斯！ 嘿 伙计们
Josh! Evans!  Hey, fellas.
霍尔心村怎么样？ 嘿
How's Hallheart Village treating ya?  Hey.
你看过他们拍的那部同性恋电影吗？
Did you see the gay movie that they did?
那部电影很有吸引力
It was kind of dope.
是的 多年来他们忽视了我们
Yeah, for years they ignored us
然后他们的观众对同性恋的憎恶减少了10%
then their audience got 10% less homophobic
所以他们认为我们是一个新的人口群体
so they decided we're a new demographic
可以卖给他们的任何东西 我的意思是 看看这些电影
they can sell shit to. I mean, look at these movies.
祝你有一个异性恋的小圣诞节
Have Yourself A Heteronormative Little Christmas.
仅一位男同的《34街的奇迹》
Miracle on 34th Street but with One Gay Guy.
莎拉·鲍尔森参演的《独自在家》
Home Alone but with Sarah Paulson.
我的意思是 这太荒谬了  乔希
I mean, it's absurd.  Josh.
嘿 圣诞快乐
Hey.  Merry Christmas.
来拿溜冰鞋
Come get skates.
我想看到你和亚伦
I want to see you and Aaron
回到冰面上 像往常的日子一样
back out on the ice for old times' sake.
是的
Yeah.
鲍比 乔希和亚伦
Bobby, Josh and Aaron
在高中时一起打冰球
played hockey together in high school.
哦 我知道  是的
Oh, I know.  Yeah.
来吧  嘿 伙计 发生什么事了？
Come on.  Hey, man, what's going on?
伙计 你有什么问题吗？ 什么？
Dude, what is your problem?  What?
你能不能 少讲一点那些东西？
Could you just, like, maybe tone it down a notch?
我很抱歉 我不明白
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
我们已经和我父母在一起两个小时了
We've been with my parents for two hours
你已经谈到了变性人模型
and you've already talked about transgender mannequins
艾滋病预防
HIV prevention
你还指出了1976年Dyke游行的路线
and you pointed out the route to the 1976 Dyke March.
他们听着很开心啊 他们完全没觉得什么
They're having fun. They're totally fine.
你的问题是什么？
What is your problem?
我很紧张 好吗？
I'm nervous, okay?
我从来没有把他们介绍给任何人
I've never introduced them to anybody.
我只是不想让他们感到奇怪
I just don't want them to get weirded out.
我想让他们有一个放松而又普通的时光
I want them to have, like, a chill, normal time.
所以现在我不正常了？
So now I'm not normal?
鲍比 你知道我的意思
Bobby, you know what I mean.
我只是在做我自己
I'm just being myself.
好吧 但也许你可以
Okay, but maybe you could just be, like
少做一点自己 也就三个小时
a little less yourself for like three hours.
我想让他们喜欢你
I want them to like you.
哦 是的
Oh. Yeah.
不 当然 当然了
No, sure. Of course.
是的 我只是...
Yeah, I'll just...
我就不说话了
I'll just be quiet.
好的 谢谢你
Okay, thank you.
鲍比！哦 我的天！
Bobby! Oh, my God!
嗨！
Hi!
嗨！我的天
Hi!  Jesus Christ.
我们还是得去 我们预订了晚餐
We have to go anyway. We have a dinner reservation.
晚餐又在哪里？
Where's dinner again?
我在飞
♪ I'm flying ♪
看着我 高高在上
♪ Look at me, way up high ♪
突然间 我在这里
♪ Suddenly, here am I ♪
我在飞翔
♪ I'm flying. ♪
嘿 爸爸 北极熊队怎么样了？
Hey, Dad, how are the Polar Bears doing?
那是我和乔希以前玩的球队
That's the team Josh and I used to play on.
他们整年都没有赢过
They haven't won all year.
我告诉乔希他们需要你们回来
I told Josh they need you boys to come back.
鲍比 你今晚看起来很安静
Bobby, you seem quiet tonight.
一切都还好吗？
Is everything all right?
噢 我完全没事 是的
Oh, yeah, I'm totally fine. Yeah.
我其实 我很抱歉
I'm actually  You know, I'm sorry
如果我今天说了太多的话
if I spoke too much today.
我只是... ... 我想我有点紧张
I just  I think I got nervous.
这其实更像我平时的样子
This is actually more like how I usually am.
我非常安静
I'm very quiet.
非常安静 古怪而又正常
Very quiet and just, like, weirdly normal.
好吧 再次感谢
Well, thanks again
筹划了这样一个美好的一天
for planning such a lovely day.
噢 不用谢 谢泼德夫人
Oh, you're so welcome, Mrs. Shepard.
哦 你听起来像我的一个学生
Oh, you sound like one of my students.
叫我安妮就好了
Call me Anne.
好的 我会的
Okay, I will.
呃 妈妈一直是一个二年级的老师
Uh, Mom's been a second grade teacher
近40年了
for almost 40 years now.
噢 我的天 这太不可思议了
Oh, my God, that's amazing.
我们需要好老师 现在比以往任何时候都更需要
We need good teachers, now more than ever.
谢谢你 我同意
Thank you. I agree.
而亚伦说你在美国历史博物馆工作
And Aaron says you're working at an American history museum.
是的 是的
Yes. Yes, it is.
是一个美国历史博物馆
It's an American history museum.
嗯
Hmm.
嗯 嗯
Mm hmm.
嗯 实际上是一个LGBTQ历史博物馆
Well, it's actually an LGBTQ history museum.
是美国第一个大型酷儿历史博物馆
It's the first major queer history museum in America.
你有教你的学生任何同性恋历史吗？
Do you teach your students any gay history?
因为我知道在一些州
'Cause I know in a few states
他们终于开始这样做了
they're finally starting to do it.
嗯 我教二年级 所以没有
Well, I teach second grade, so no.
哦 对
Oh, right.
不 我理解 是的
No, I understand. Yeah.
出于好奇 为什么不呢？
Out of curiosity, why not?
嗯 我只是觉得
Well, I just think
他们还小 不适合了解这些
they're a little young for that.
哦 当然了 是的
Oh, of course. Yeah.
是的 我明白这一点
No, I understand that.
不过我不这么认为
I don't think so, though.
啊 鲍比  不 不 不 我只是说说
Ah, Bobby.  No, no, no, I'm just saying.
如果我可以恭敬地提出不同意见的话
If I may disagree respectfully.
这实际上是最好的时机
That's actually the best time
去教他们 趁他们年轻的时候
to teach them, when they're young.
你知道 这样他们就会理解同性恋
You know, that way they develop an appreciation
在他们要开始互相霸凌之前
for queer people before they all start bullying each other
或是 因为自己是同性恋而憎恨自己
or hating themselves if they're gay.
也许你是对的
Maybe you're right.
哦
Oh.
但感觉还是有点年轻
Feels a little young, though.
嗯 对
Hmm. Right.
完全正确 我明白了
Totally. I get it.
我不说了
I will drop it.   Yeah.
搁置争议先 是的
Agree to disagree.  Yeah.
为之欢呼
Cheers to that.  Yes.
嘿 那么 呃 你们什么时候回家... ...
Hey, so, uh, when are you guys heading home...
不过其实也没那么年轻
It's not really that young, though.
没那么年轻
It's not that young.
鲍比 你能不能别说了？
Bobby, can you please drop it?
不 我不能 因为我们在谈论的是同性恋孩子
No, I can't, because we're talking about gay kids here
而且这很重要
and it's important.
拯救我的其中一件事是
One of the things that saved me is that
我的父母在我小的时候让我接触到同性恋的故事
my parents exposed me to gay stories when I was a kid.
当我12岁的时候   这是真的
When I was 12 years old  this is true
我的父母带我去看了一部百老汇戏剧
my parents took me to see a Broadway play
叫做《爱与同情》
called Love and Compassion.
它是关于一群同性恋者
It was about a group of gay men
一起在普罗旺斯镇度过夏天
spending the summer together in Provincetown.
突然间 大幕拉开了
And all of a sudden, the curtain goes up
舞台上出现了七个全裸的同性恋
and there are seven completely naked gay men onstage.
而我就在那里 坐在我妈妈和爸爸之间
And there I am, sitting between my mom and dad
12岁 看着七个还没硬起来的阴茎
at age 12, looking at seven soft penises.
然后突然间
Shit.  And all of a sudden
两个家伙开始亲热
two of the guys start making out
然后他们中的一个开始 说粗口 你知道吗？
and then one of them starts, like, talking dirty, you know?
我记得很清楚
And I remember this so vividly.
有一个性爱场景 其中一个家伙说：
There was a sex scene, and one of the guys is like
"狠狠的干我 狠狠的干我 "
"Pound my prostate. Pound my prostate."
"操射我 操射我"
You know, "Milk me. Milk me."
而我甚至不知道那是什么
And I didn't even know what that was.
我的意思是 现在我知道了
I mean, now I do.
但是 你知道 那是不可思议的
But, you know, it was incredible.
你知道 要知道 我可以坐在那里
You know, to know that I could sit there
在我妈妈和爸爸之间 看着七个阴茎
between my mom and dad, looking at seven penises.
七个阴茎 安妮
Seven penises, Anne.
我当时12岁
I was 12.
而且知道他们可以接受这个 我的意思是
And to know that they were okay with that, I mean
这对我产生了深远的影响
that had a profound effect on me.
我想说的是 我们需要消除这类事情的耻辱感
All I'm saying is, we need to remove the stigma
从这种类型的事情 让同性恋的孩子
from that type of thing so that gay kids
可以对自己感觉良好 这就是我要说的
can feel good about themselves. That's all I'm saying.
我是说 看看亚伦 看看他有多恨自己的生活
I mean, look at Aaron and how much he hates his life.
鲍比  不 我想说的是
Bobby.  No, all I'm saying is there's
你对自己的生活有多不满意
a direct correlation between how unhappy you are
与你小时候没有被教育到的可能性
with your life and what you weren't taught
有直接关系
about your potential as a child.
鲍比 别说话了
Bobby, stop talking.
什么...  说真的 够了
Wh...  Seriously, enough.
我要杀了你
I will kill you.
亚伦 你讨厌你的生活？
Aaron, you hate your life?
♪ Rama lama lama ka dinga da dinga dong ♪
♪ Shoo bop sha wadda wadda yippity boom de boom ♪
♪ Chang chang changitty chang sha bop ♪
♪ Dip da dip da dip doo wop da doo bee doo ♪
♪ Boogedy boogedy boogedy boogedy ♪
♪ Shoo be doo wop she bop ♪
♪ Sha na na na na na na na ♪
♪ Yippity boom de boom ♪
♪ Wop ba ba lu mop and wop bam boom. ♪
你哥哥真的是个话匣子
Your brother's a real chatterbox.
嘿 你疯了吗？
Hey, are you mad?
我？ 不 我很好
Me? No, I'm great.
乔希只是发短信给我
Josh just texted me.
我要去那个酒吧见他
I'm gonna meet him at that bar.
我想我们应该回家谈谈这个
I think we should go home and talk about this.
哦 真的吗？你想再谈谈？
Oh, really? You want to talk more?
好吧 我想这比和乔希去参加聚会要好
Well, I think it's better than going to party with Josh
那个自我厌恶的类固醇傻子 花了40年时间才出柜
the self loathing meathead who took 40 years to come out.
是啊 不是每个人都是你 鲍比
Yeah, well, not everybody's you, Bobby.
好吧 但40年？
Okay, but 40 years?
J.R.R.托尔金花在旅途的时间都要少一点
J.R.R. Tolkien took less time with his journey.
天啊 你真他妈的无情
God, you are fucking relentless.
"亚伦痛恨他的生活"？
"Aaron hates his life"?
上帝啊
God.
嘿
Hey.
嘿！
Hey!
操！
Fuck!
噢 好吧 好吧
Oh, oh, oh, oh. Okay, okay, okay, okay.
很好
Good man.
啊 老兄 不 不
Ah, dude. No.
嘿 吻我就好
Hey, just kiss me.
亚伦
Aaron.
哦 嘿 鲍勃
Oh, hey, Bob.
呃 妈的 鲍比 我们只是在玩玩
Uh, shit, Bobby, we were just playing around.
这 这  你们只是在玩玩？
It's it's...  You were just playing around?
你他妈的有什么毛病？
What the fuck is wrong with you?
鲍比 鲍比  乔什 请你离开  我很抱歉
Bobby, Bobby.  Josh, leave.  I'm sorry.
他妈的给我滚出去！
Get the fuck out of here!
鲍比 冷静点  噢 我的天 我就知道
Bobby, calm down.  Oh, my God, I knew it.
我他妈的就知道
I fucking knew it.
快说吧
Just say it.
你能不能直接说出来？
Can you please just say it?
都这时候了 你他妈的说出来啊 因为我已经知道了
Finally, just fucking say it, because I already know.
你对我没有吸引力  什么？
You're not attracted to me.  What?
我看到你看的那些人 在健身房和俱乐部
I see the guys you look at, at the gym and the club.
每一个地方！我们去的每一个地方！
Everywhere! Everywhere we go!
好吧 鲍比...  去和他在一起吧
Okay, Bobby...  Go be with him
如果那是你想要的 但我不会让你
if that's what you want, but I will not let you
但我不会让你再把我拖进这件事了  这不是...
drag me into this any further.  It's not...
我也不会让你伤我的心
And I will not let you break my heart.
我太聪明了！
I am too smart for that!
鲍比 你为什么要在我父母面前
Bobby, why did you say that shit about me
说我的坏话？
in front of my parents?
我求你不要让我难堪
I begged you not to embarrass me
但你还是控制不住自己
but you couldn't help yourself.
你有什么毛病？
What is wrong with you?
我有什么毛病？
What is wrong with me?
"小声点 鲍比 "
"Tone it down, Bobby."
"安静点 鲍比 "
"Be quiet, Bobby."
"你就不能少做一点自己吗？
"Can't you be a little bit less of yourself
就这几个小时？"
just for a few hours?"
你以为我不知道那是什么意思？
You don't think I know what that means?
你以为我不知道意味着什么吗？
You don't think I know what that's code for?
你以为我不知道吗？
You don't think I've been hearing that
我的一生？
my whole fucking life?
这就是你对我的看法？
That's what you think about me?
我不会为自己道歉的 我将把这个问题留给你
I'm not apologizing for myself. I will leave that to you.
嘿 问你个问题 因为你认识所有人
Hey, question for you because you know everyone.
我需要改头换面
I need a makeover.
噢 让我们去做个周末水疗吧
Ooh, yeah. Let's go to a spa weekend.
不 我想要类固醇或者 比如
No, I want steroids or, like
睾丸激素或HGH什么的
testosterone or HGH or something.
我一直在锻炼 但我没有变大块
I keep working out, but I don't get bigger.
我想看起来像一个他妈的动作明星
I want to look like a fucking action star.
忘记普罗旺斯镇 我想让人们认为
Forget Provincetown. I want people to think
我在《勇敢者的游戏》上有一席之地
I have a summer share on Jumanji.
我已经厌倦了做普通人 我想成为雷神
I'm sick of being niche. I want to be Thor.
鲍比 你知道 类固醇
Bobby, you know that steroids
并不能让你自己变大 对吗？
don't make you big on their own, right?
比如说 你还是得锻炼身体
Like, you still have to work out
而且你不能错过窗口期  我知道！
and you can't miss the window.  I know!
我们他妈的走吧
Let's fucking go.
噢
Ow.
不
No.
操！ 不！
Fuck!
不 你在干什么？
No! What are you doing?!
别这样！ 鲍比！鲍比！
Stop that!  Bobby! Bobby!
林肯的展览被取消了  为什么？
The Lincoln exhibit is canceled.  Why?
人们在威胁要进行抵制
People are threatening a boycott.
他们正在撤消他们的捐款
They're pulling their donations.
因为没有足够的证据
There's just not enough proof.
好吧
Okay.
你想把林肯放回柜子里？好啊！
You want to put Lincoln back in the closet? Fine!
我会把他放回柜子里的！ 鲍比
I'll put him back in the closet!  Bobby.
我要把他放回他妈的衣柜里！ 鲍比
I'll put him back in the fucking closet!  Bobby.
这里！
Here!
这就对了！
There you go!
林肯又回到了你们都需要他的柜子里了！
Lincoln is back in the closet where you all need him to be!
我在吃类固醇！
I'm on steroids!
好了 鲍比 冷静点
Okay, Bobby, just calm down.
所以 安吉拉和我提议
So, Angela and I have proposed
最后的展览被称为 "后同性恋"
that the final exhibit be called "Post Gay."
后同性恋？
Post Gay?
是的 因为只要是同性恋就已经是旧闻了
Yes, because just being gay is old news.
好吧 意思是 现在我对亚伦来说太同性恋了
Okay, so, now I'm too gay for Aaron
但我对你来说却太直了？
but I'm too straight for you?
谁能告诉我
Will somebody please tell me
谁能告诉我 我到底应该是怎样的同性恋？
exactly how gay I'm supposed to be?!
可怜的亚伯拉罕 林肯现在甚至不能成为同性恋了？
Poor Abraham Lincoln can't even be gay now?!
因为他不是同性恋 鲍比
Because he wasn't gay, Bobby.
他是双性恋 而我有...  好了 够了！
He was bi, and I have...  Okay, enough!
你想删掉我们的故事？好吧！
You want to get rid of our stories? Fine!
让我们摆脱他们！
Let's get rid of them!
我有类固醇的愤怒！
I have roid rage!
你疯了吗？
Are you insane?
鲍比...  是的 拜拜 布蒂吉格！
Bobby...  Yeah, bye bye, Buttigieg!
别这样 鲍比  不！
Stop it, Bobby.  No!
鲍比！ 给  不！
Bobby!  Give  No!
把它给我！
Give it to me!
把旗子放下！ 不！把它给我！
Put the flag down!  No! Give it to me!
把它给...
Give it to...
安吉拉 女同性恋们 按住他
Angela and the lesbians, hold him down.
不！
No!
你在吃类固醇？ 你不能说
You're on steroids?  You can't tell.
你知道吗？我不需要这些破东西
You know what? I don't need this shit.
我也不需要
Me neither.
女同性恋们 散开！
Lesbians, disperse!
我讨厌这个博物馆
I hate the museum
但最重要的是 我真的他妈的讨厌讲故事
but most of all, I really fucking hate storytelling.
她不喜欢讲故事
She doesn't like telling stories.
也许最后一翼应该是
Maybe the final wing should be
一个大的空房间 人们可以去
a big empty room where people can go
闭上他妈的嘴！
to just shut the fuck up!
好的 是的
Okay. Yeah.
离开！你们所有人！
Leave! All of you!
哦 该死 我的窗口期
Oh, shit, my window.
我的锻炼窗口期！
My workout window!
来点节奏
♪ Drop the bass. ♪
嘿 兄弟
Hey, bro.
嘿 兄弟 怎么了？ 怎么了？
Hey, bro. What's up?  What's up?
我是乔尔
I'm Joel.
我是... 罗伯
I'm... Rob.
嘿 你能帮我弄一下器材吗 兄弟？
Hey, can you help me with this set, bro?
当然 兄弟
Yeah, sure, bro. Yeah.
很好
Nice.
你在做胸部锻炼吗？ 是的
You doing chest?  Yep.
我是大腿日 兄弟  哦 不错
Leg day for me, bro.  Oh, nice.
得好好练练腿部肌肉
Got to work on those hammies.
是啊
Yeah.
把它们都放上去吧
Go put them all on.
今天要做一个超级组合
Doing a superset today.
哦 超级组合？ 是的
Oh, superset?  Yeah.
是的 超级组合
Yeah, superset.
收拾一下 兄弟
Pack it up, bro.
很多盘子  是的
Lots of plates.  Yeah.
我还没有见过这么多盘子
I haven't seen this many plates
自从 犹太人的节日 兄弟
since, uh, the Jewish holidays, bro.
不错 不错  是啊
Nice, nice.  Yeah.
我们应该找个时间再聚聚
We should hang out again sometime.
也许看一场比赛？
Maybe watch a game?
好的 我可以
Yeah, I'd love that.
我留个电话给你
I'll give you my number.
我靠 老兄 你的声音怎么了？
Holy shit, dude. What happened to your voice?
哦 他妈的
Oh, fuck.
嗯 好吧 我真的很抱歉
Um, okay, I'm really sorry.
但是 嗯  我知道这是非常奇怪的
But, um  I know this is very strange
但是 当我 我 当我在健身房走到你身边
but when I I, when I walked up to you in the gym
我就发出了这种声音 你知道吗？
I I just did this voice, you know?
就像 你知道 就像
Like, you know, like
"嘿 兄弟 怎么了？"
"Hey, bro. What's up?"
我不知道
I I don't know.
我只是在尝试
I just was trying it.
妈的 你是一个连环杀手？
Holy shit, are you a serial killer?
你他妈的现在要杀掉一个兄弟吗？
Are you gonna fucking kill a bro right now?
不 不 不 我没有要杀兄弟 我很抱歉
No, no, no. I'm not killing a bro. I'm so sorry.
不 这很奇怪 我很抱歉 我要走了
No, this is weird. I'm sorry. I'll go.
是的 你需要现在就离开
Yeah, you need to leave right now.
但它还是起了点作用 不是吗？
But it kind of worked, right?
这就是它的奇怪之处... ...
Like, that's what's weird about it...
伙计 快点 伙计
Dude, hurry up, man.
我知道 事实上我就好像
I know, but just the fact that I was like
"嘿 兄弟 怎么了？"
"Hey, bro. What's up?"
好吧 我走了
Okay, I'm leaving.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我现在正在经历一个非常艰难的时期
I'm going through a very hard time right now.
我没有要求你做这些  好吧
I ain't ask for all that.  Okay.
我很抱歉 我要走了 我走了
I'm sorry. I'm going. I'm going.
不过 我可以问你一件事吗？
Can I just ask you one thing, though?
如果我走到你面前 用我真实的声音 你会不会被吸引？
If I had come up to you and used my real voice
你会被我吸引吗？
would you have been attracted to me?
哇
Wow.
这真的很可悲 但是...
That is really sad, but...
我想会的
Yeah, I think so.
哦
Oh.
但不是现在
But not now.
好吧
Okay.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
史翠珊？ 当然了
Streisand?  Of course.
我爱她
I love her.
她是最棒的  史翠珊秒了
She's the best.  Streisand fucking rules.
这其实有点像Yentl 如果你仔细想想
This is actually kind of like Yentl, if you think about it.
伙计 你他妈的给我滚出去！ 我很抱歉
Dude, get the fuck out!  I'm so sorry.
以后再说
Later.
对不起
Sorry.
现在 Hallheart自豪地介绍
And now, Hallheart proudly presents
我们的第一部多角关系的节日电影
our first polyamorous holiday film
冬青色的多角恋圣诞节
A Holly, Poly Christmas.
看 下雪了
Look, it's snowing.
我们七个人都在下雪
It's snowing on all seven of us.
哦 伙计
Oh, man.
嘿
Hey.
我们能谈谈吗？
Can we talk?
好的
Okay.
那么 怎么了？
So, what's up?
鲍比 我很抱歉我告诉你不要做你自己
Bobby, I am so sorry I told you not to be yourself.
我知道我搞砸了 但这对我来说也很新鲜
I know I fucked up, but this is new for me, too.
当你在我父母面前大发雷霆的时候 说实话 这...
And when you blew up in front of my parents, honestly, it...
...感觉你是故意这样做的
...it felt like you were doing it on purpose.
我就是故意的
I was.
而且我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
我不应该那样处理 你是对的
I shouldn't have handled it like that. You're right.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
但是 亚伦
But, Aaron
这并不能改变的事实
that doesn't change the fact that
你喜欢某种类型的人
you like a certain type of guy.
而那不是我 那也没关系
And that isn't me, and that's okay.
你是对的
You're right.
我总是想象自己和一个男人... ...
I always pictured myself with a guy...
就像乔希  是的 像乔希那样的人
Like Josh.  Yeah, a guy like Josh.
是的 他很性感
Yeah, he's hot.
是的 他很简单 很传统 很基本
Yes, he's simple, conventional, basic as hell
而不是真正能让我开心的人
and not somebody that actually makes me happy.
鲍比 你和我是如此不同
Bobby, you are so different from me.
你不害怕在这个世界上占据空间
You're not afraid to take up space in the world.
你敢于挑战我
You challenge me.
起初 这让我很害怕
Which at first, it freaked me out
因为谁他妈的想一直被挑战？
because who the fuck wants to be challenged all the time?
但是...
But...
但是 我喜欢这样
But I love it.
你是我们所缺少的
You're what's been missing.
我知道我搞砸了 但请再给我一次机会
I know I fucked up, but please give me another chance.
我非常想念你
I miss you so much.
我也想你
I miss you, too.
非常想
A lot.
直到我们分手后 我才意识到
I didn't realize until after we broke up
其实在那几个月里 ...
there were actually a couple of months there where I was...
他们怎么说来着？
What do they call it?
我心情还不错
In a good mood.
但我不能
But I can't.
在我的一生中 我一直为自己有自知之明而自豪
My whole life, I have prided myself on being self aware
以及自力更生和自我控制
and self reliant and self possessed
但这并不重要
and it didn't matter.
这并不重要 因为一天结束下来
It didn't matter because, at the end of the day
我只是在街上走了一圈
I just ended up in the street
看着你 看着乔希
looking at you and looking at Josh
并想 "我对他来说还不够 "
and thinking, "I'm not enough for him."
我知道 而且我感觉很糟糕
I know, and I feel awful
但不要因为一个错误而放弃这个机会！
but do not throw this away because of one mistake!
你想让我怎么做？
Wh What do you want me to do?
说你会再给我一次机会
Say you'll give me another chance.
我不能这么做
I can't do that.
为什么不能？
Why not?
因为我不相信你
'Cause I don't trust you.
我已经孤独了这么久 谁知道呢？
I've been alone so long, who knows?
也许这是我唯一知道的方式
Maybe that's the only way I know how to be.
我不知道
I don't know.
我要走了
I'm going.
这很好
It's good.
嘿！
Hey!
如果你不相信我 那也没关系
If you don't trust me, that's fine.
但如果出于某种原因
But if for some reason
在所有这些力量和信心之下
underneath all that strength and confidence
你仍然不相信你是足够可爱的
you still don't trust that you are lovable enough
我就是活生生的证据...
I'm living proof...
证明你错了
that you're wrong.
首先 感谢你们所有人
First of all, thank you all
让我做这个
for letting me do this.
我真的很感激
I really appreciate it.
听着 我知道我一直是
Look, I know I've been
很明显 我是一个非常愤怒、爱评判的人
a very angry, judgmental person, obviously.
而有时愤怒可以是好事
And sometimes anger can be good.
我知道你们都知道 因为 多年来
I know you all know that because, for years
它是我们都需要的燃料 以便我们继续前进
it was the fuel we all needed to keep going.
不久以前 世界上的异性恋守门人还不允许
It wasn't that long ago that the straight gatekeepers
我们所有的人
of the world didn't allow for all of us
真正获得巨大的成功
to really succeed in a big way.
噢 我的天 你们还记得异性恋们吗？
Oh, my God. Do you guys remember straight people?
是啊 他们有过好一轮了
Yeah, they had a nice run.
听着 鲍比 我是一个黑人变性女人 我不需要你
Look, Bobby, I'm a Black trans woman, and I don't need you
到这里来教育我保持愤怒
to come here and lecture me about anger.
但我明白
But I get it.
我充满了
I am brimming
愤怒
with anger.
如果我只是去发泄一点
And if I were to let just an ounce of it out
我都可能会爆发 把你们每个人都杀了
I would probably explode and kill every one of you.
但是 鲍比 我想让你知道一些事情
But, Bobby, I want you to know something.
我听到了你的声音
I hear you.
而且我原谅你
And I forgive you.
你原谅了？
You do?
是的
Yes.
听着 这是我唯一
Look, this is the only community
一直想要成为其中的一部分的社区
I've ever loved being a part of.
虽然我们疯狂地争吵 而且一直如此 但...
And we fight like crazy, and we always have, but...
...你们是我的家人
...you're my people.
我很抱歉 我对你们如此无礼 对你们说三道四
And I am so sorry that I was so rude and spoke down to you.
我应该对你们表示更多的尊重
I should've shown you much more respect.
地球上确实没有其他
There is truly no group of people on earth
我更爱和更尊重的人
that I love and respect more.
好吧 我不打算撒谎 我仍然很生气
Well, I am not going to lie. I am still angry.
但我坚持要有进步 不仅仅是为我们的LGBTQ英雄们
But I insist on progress, not just for our LGBTQ heroes
而是为我们的LGBTQ混蛋
but for our LGBTQ assholes.
就像你
Like you.
谢谢你 罗伯特
Thank you, Robert.
这次道歉的直播有4万多人观看
The live of this apology has like 40K viewers.
你要发布这个？
You're posting this?
你能不能...
Can you please
不可以 好吧
No, okay. Yeah.
不 你还是去发布吧
No, you should definitely post this.
一切都应该...都应该大肆宣传
Everything should... everything should be posted
谢谢你教我这个
and thank you for teaching me that.
不要离开
♪ Don't leave ♪
不要哭
♪ Don't cry ♪
你只是另一个被卷入麦田的男孩
♪ You're just another boy caught in the rye ♪
嘿 我决定辞职了
Hey. I've decided to quit.
我也刚辞职  是吗？
I just quit, too.  You did?
我在网上模仿卡马拉 哈里斯
I do this Kamala Harris impression online
而且 真的蒸蒸日上
and it's really taken off.
哦 是啊 就像
Oh.  Yeah, like
我是卡马拉 哈里斯
I'm Kamala Harris.
好吗？
Okay?
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
是的 不管你在做什么 祝你好运
Yeah, good luck with whatever you're doing.
谢谢你
Thank you.
嘿 鲍比 我想让你成为第一个看到这个的人
Hey, Bobby, I wanted you to be the first person to see this.
这是亚伦 谢泼德的巧克力工厂
This is Aaron Shepard's Chocolate Factory.
我做了这些小巧克力
I made these little chocolates.
我还做了一些特别的点心
I also made some special treats
来庆祝LGBTQ+博物馆的开幕
to celebrate the opening of the LGBTQ+ Museum.
这些是Harvey Milk Duds
These are Harvey Milk Duds.
而不是一个装满了巧克力
And instead of a heart shaped Valentine's Day box
心形的情人节盒子 我们有一个里面装满了巧克力
filled with chocolates, we have a pink
"沉默等于死亡 "的粉红色三角形盒子
"silence equals death" triangle filled with chocolates.
还有一个向我最喜欢的同性恋电视角色致敬的东西
And a tribute to my favorite gay television character
这就是...
this is...
《老友记》中的提拉米苏 苏珊
a Tirami Susan from Friends.
亚伦 当然喜欢《老友记》
Of course Aaron likes Friends.
当然 所有的利润都给了博物馆
Of course, all the profits go to the museum.
好的
Okay.
再见
Bye.
没事的
♪ It's all right ♪
一切都会好起来的
♪ It's all right. ♪
老兄 谢谢你让我住在这里
Dude, thanks for letting me crash here.
我知道是妈妈给你施压邀请我 但是...
I know Mom pressured you into inviting me, but...
你真好
it's cool of you.
是啊 当然
Yeah, sure.
你还好吗 兄弟？ 是的 我很好
You okay, bro?  Yeah, I'm fine.
我是一个非常快乐的巧克力师
I'm a very happy chocolatier.
我是说 有个家伙
I mean, there was that guy.
但它已经结束了 不管怎么样 我很好
But it's over. Whatever. I'm fine.
是啊 完全
Yeah, totally.
我的天 你是怎么斩首的？
Jesus, how do you decapitate?
说真的 这就是你想说的？
Seriously, that's all you're gonna say?
"你是怎么斩首的？"
"How do you decapitate?"
你想让我说什么？你怎么砍掉他们的头？
What do you want me to say? How do you remove their heads?
为什么不问问 "嘿 兄弟 你怎么样了？
What about, "Hey, bro, how are you doing?
你是怎么坚持下来的？"
How are you holding up?"
我很抱歉 兄弟 我们不谈这些破事
I'm sorry, bro. We don't talk about this shit.
我在这里睡觉 是因为我正在办理离婚手续
I'm I'm crashing here because I'm in the middle of a divorce
而你一次也没有问过我
and you haven't asked me about it once.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
那么 离婚的事怎么样了？
So, how's the divorce?
我不想谈论它  好吧
I don't want to talk about it.  Okay.
那么...
So...
...你发生了什么？
...what happened to you?
好吧 你还记得圣诞节时 爸爸妈妈来了吗？
Okay, you remember at Christmas when Mom and Dad came?
我让鲍比...
I asked Bobby to...
我让他小点声
I asked him to tone it down.
我知道 我搞砸了 我慌了
I know. I know. I fucked up. I panicked.
你有没有尝试
Did you try
让他回来还是...  是的
to get him back or...  Yes.
我的意思是 鲍比是最好的
I mean, Bobby is the best
但他也是个顽固的狗东西
but he is a stubborn son of a bitch.
而你爱这个顽固的狗东西吗？
And do you love this stubborn little bitch?
随便吧 一切都结束了
Whatever. It's over.
鲍比很坚强 他不需要我
Bobby's strong. He doesn't need me.
他不需要任何人
He doesn't need anyone.
如此活着
♪ So alive ♪
爱上这种感觉 理解这种意义...
♪ Loving the feeling, learning the meaning... ♪
嘿 伙计们 这是你的女孩塔玛拉
Hey, guys. It's your girl Tamara.
我们今晚要为LGBT博物馆开幕
We're opening the LGBT Museum tonight.
今晚是我们的盛大开幕
Tonight is our grand opening
我们会有一个美好的时光！
and we're gonna have a wonderful time!
耶！
Yeah!
怎么了？ 怎么了？  怎么了？
What's up?  What's up?
嗨 我是莱昂纳多 达芬奇
Hi. I'm Leonardo da Vinci.
我以我的工作改变了世界
I changed the world with my work
作为一个发明家、科学家和艺术家改变了世界
as an inventor, scientist and artist.
但最重要的是 我可能是双性恋
But most importantly, I may have been bi.
请进
Arrivederci.
祝贺你 你终于撑到了奥巴马政府
Congrats. You've made it to the Obama administration.
但转角处的是什么？
But what's that around the corner?
好吧 说真的 这个地方真是不可思议
Okay, seriously, this place is incredible.
你高兴吗？ 我不知道
Are you happy?  I don't know.
这很奇怪 你知道吗？
It's weird, you know?
就像 这个地方是我的梦想 然后就发生了
Like, this place was my dream, then it happened.
为什么我不能回答你的问题？
Why can't I answer your question?
好吧 我能说说吗？ 是的
Okay, can I just say one thing?  Yes.
我知道他所做的事是错的
I know that what he did was wrong
但你没有必要和他的父母争论
but you didn't have to argue with his parents.
但是 我做了 另外 我已经道歉了
I did, though. Plus, I apologized.
他也道歉了
And he apologized, too.
我只是不知道我是否能相信他
I just don't know if I can trust him.
他搞砸了 人都会犯错
He fucked up. People fuck up.
难道没有一部分的你
Is there no part of you
想给他第二次机会？
that wants to give him a second chance?
你知道那是什么吗？
You know what it is?
我只是不想这么需要别人
I just don't want to want someone else this much.
但你想
But you do.
爱一个人并不会让你看起来很脆弱
It doesn't make you look weak to love someone.
脆弱并不是勃起的杀手
Vulnerability is not a boner killer.
我了解你
I know you.
我知道你有无数的理由
I know that you've had a million reasons
让你这些年一直保持警惕
to keep your guard up all these years.
但是有一些人在那里
But there are people out there
值得你放松警惕
worth letting your guard down for.
有他或没有他 你是否更快乐？
Were you happier with him or without him?
那才是真正重要的
That's all that really matters.
我可以告诉你一些只能告诉你
Can I tell you something extremely embarrassing
的极其尴尬的事情吗？
that I would only tell you?
是的
Yes.
我写了一首关于他的歌
I wrote a song about him.
我知道! 这是唯一一次
I know! That's the only time
谈论它
I'm ever gonna talk about it.
以后都不会谈论了
We're not talking about it.
我没有发给他 我也不会发给他
I didn't send it, and I'm not sending it.
好吧 很好
Okay. Fine.
我只是从来没有见过你那开心
I've just never seen you that happy is all.
而且我喜欢看到开心的你
And I love seeing it.
嗨 伙计们
Hi, guys.
嗨 亲爱的  准备好去跳舞了吗？
Hi, sweetie.  Ready to go dance?
是的 我们走吧
Yeah.  Let's go.
妈的 他给我发了短信
Holy shit. He texted me.
鲍比给我发了短信！ 嗯 他说什么？
Bobby texted me!  Well, what'd he say?
他说 "嘿 怎么了？"
He said, "Hey, what's up?"
"嘿 怎么了？"
"Hey, what's up?"
他妈的好啊 兄弟！ 是吗？
Fuck yeah, bro!  Yeah?
这就是我要说的！ 是吗？这很好吗？是的！
That's what I'm talking about!  Yeah? That's good? Yeah!
很好！"嘿 怎么了？"
It's great! "Hey, what's up?"
"嘿 怎么了？" "嘿 怎么了？"
"Hey, what's up?" "Hey, what's up?"
不 等等 不 等一下 等一下  什么？
No, wait. No, wait, wait.  What?
好吧 是的
Okay, yeah.
我 我打算等等给他回短信 不过 你知道吗？
I I'm gonna wait to text him back, though, you know?
啊 该死 我得去健身房了
Ah, shit. I got to get to the gym.
亚伦 你他妈的怎么回事 每天都在做CrossFit吗？
Aaron, what the fuck is up with you and the CrossFit every day?
天啊！你们这些人都在训练什么？
Jesus! What are you people all training for?
你是要去打仗吗？
You going to war?
别装得那么酷了
Stop playing it so cool.
去告诉他你的感受吧
Just go and tell him how you feel.
哦 那你呢？离婚怎么办？
Oh, what about you? What about divorce?
保持年轻和乐趣呢？
What about keeping it young and fun?
哦 随便吧
Oh, whatever.
异性恋...  我们的方式太固定了
Straight people  we're so set in our ways.
但是同性恋者... 你们都是那么...
But gay people  you guys are all so
你们是如此的聪明
you're so smart.
你们会想出办法的
You're gonna figure it out.
我的故事不是你的故事
My story is not your story.
去书写你自己该死的故事吧
Go write your own damn story.
去吧！现在！ 好吧 是的
Go! Now!  Okay. Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
"嘿 怎么了？"
"Hey, what's up?"
"嘿 怎么了？" 是的！ "嘿 怎么了？"
"Hey, what's up?" Yeah!  "Hey, what's up?"
鲍比？ 是吗？
Bobby?  Yeah?
到了敬酒的时候了  好的 太好了
It's time for the toast.  Okay, great.
好的
Okay.
把博物馆放在一起的最困难的部分之一
One of the hardest parts of putting the museum together
就是要弄清楚最后的展品是什么
was figuring out what the final exhibit would be.
我们要给人们留下关于我们是谁的信息
The message we'd leave people with about who we are.
但事实是我们不是一个东西
But the truth is we are not one thing.
我们不是一个单一的群体
We are not a monolithic group.
我们是一些你们遇到的
We are some of the smartest and most self reliant people
最聪明和最自立的人
you will ever meet.
而我们又是如此愚蠢
And we are so stupid.
我们是混乱的
And we are a total mess.
而我们是也伟大的
And we are great.
当然 我们从一开始就已经存在了
We've been around since the beginning of time, of course
然而 仍然感觉我们是在最开始的时候
and yet it still feels like we're at the very beginning
能够讲述我们自己的故事
of being able to tell our own stories.
在许多方面 我认为我们仍然在
In many ways, I think we're still
互相了解 真的
getting to know each other, really.
现在 我只是一个无聊的顺性白人男同
Now, I'm just a boring old cis white gay
但是...
but...
我从我的变性人、双性恋和非二元性别家人
one thing I have learned from
学到的一件事是
my trans and bi and nonbinary family is that
我们所有人的幸福都来自于保持流动性
happiness for all of us comes from staying fluid
对变化保持开放
staying open to change.
敞开心扉 不要只是去做你认为的自己
Open to being more than just who you thought you were
或是 其他人认为你的你
or more than what other people assume you are.
这是对我们所有人的祝酒词
So this is a toast to all of us.
我们已经走过了漫长的道路
We've come a long way.
而且有很多人
And there are a lot of people
他们值得活到足够长的时间来参加今晚仪式
who deserved to live long enough to be here tonight.
而我们在这里 他们却不在
And we are here, and they are not.
而且我们非常幸运
And we are very lucky.
我们非常幸运
We are very lucky.
没什么可抱怨的
I have no complaints.
嘿
Hey.
嗯...
Um...
对不起 嗯  只是 嗯
Sorry, um  Just, um
还有一件事 对不起 等一下
One more thing. Sorry, hold on.
我要去做 做吧 做吧
I'm gonna do it. Let's do it. Let's do it.
你好
Hi.
所以 嗯
So, um
这是我为今晚写的一点特别的东西
this is a little special something I wrote for tonight
我没有想到我真的会有
and I didn't think I would actually have
有理由去唱它
a reason to sing it.
而且我已经很久没有在人们面前唱歌了
And I haven't sung in front of people in a very long time
所以请原谅我
so forgive me.
但是 嗯 今晚是关于爱
But, um, tonight is about love
多年来 我们已经看到了很多异性恋演员所扮演的
and we've seen a lot of tortured gay cowboys
受折磨的同性恋牛仔
played by a lot of straight actors over the years.
所以 这是一首一位同性恋牛仔对另一个同性恋牛仔的情歌
So, this is a love song from one gay cowboy to another
灵感来自于大家最喜欢的LGBTQ+偶像
inspired by everyone's favorite LGBTQ+ icon
加思 布鲁克斯
Garth Brooks.
我们在俱乐部相遇
♪ We met at the club ♪
听着玛丽亚·凯莉的混音版
♪ Mariah Carey remix on ♪
噢 穿马具的男孩
♪ Oh, the boys in harnesses ♪
你没有认出这首歌
♪ You didn't recognize the song ♪
你带我上
♪ You took me up ♪
到普罗旺斯镇
♪ Up to Provincetown ♪
在那里 多年来 离经叛道的男孩
♪ Where, for years, the deviant boys ♪
已经跑来跑去
♪ Have run around ♪
因为爱不是爱
♪ 'Cause love is not love ♪
我们的爱是真实的
♪ Our love is real ♪
我紧张得要命 要告诉你我的感受
♪ And I'm nervous as hell to tell you how I feel ♪
因为经过这么多年的奔波
♪ 'Cause after all these years of running round ♪
很高兴有人能放慢脚步
♪ It's nice to have somebody slowing down ♪
因为爱不是爱
♪ 'Cause love is not love ♪
我们的爱是自由的
♪ Our love is free ♪
我让你成为你 你让我成为我
♪ I'll let you be you and you let me be me ♪
我们可以在床上摔跤
♪ And we can wrestle on the bed ♪
我喜欢当你把我钉在地上的时候
♪ I love when you pin me to the ground ♪
但如果我告诉你我有多爱你 男孩
♪ But if I tell you how much I love you, boy ♪
你会坚持下去吗？
♪ Will you stick around? ♪
你可以把我捧得高高的
♪ And you can lift me up ♪
我会让你平静下来
♪ And I will calm you down ♪
我承认我真的很吵
♪ I've made a lot of noise ♪
但现在只有你能听到我
♪ But only you can hear me now ♪
因为爱不是爱
♪ 'Cause love is not love ♪
这种爱是真实的
♪ This love is real ♪
我希望你有同样的感觉
♪ I hope you feel the same ♪
因为这是我的感受
♪ 'Cause this is how I feel ♪
我厌倦了生气 宝贝
♪ And I'm tired of being angry, babe ♪
我厌倦了强势
♪ And I'm sick of being strong ♪
我知道有很多愤世嫉俗的混蛋
♪ And I know a lot of cynical assholes ♪
将会讨厌这首歌
♪ Who will hate this song ♪
因为是敞开心扉的话
♪ 'Cause it's an open heart ♪
是第二次机会
♪ It's a second chance ♪
是找到你的初恋
♪ It's finding your first love ♪
作为一个40岁的男人
♪ As a 40 year old man ♪
我们不一定要结婚 宝贝
♪ And we don't have to get married, babe ♪
这就是我们的浪漫
♪ This is our romance ♪
仅仅因为我们是同性恋
♪ And just because we're gay ♪
并不意味着我们必须要跳舞
♪ Doesn't mean we have to dance ♪
因为爱是不
♪ 'Cause love is not ♪
爱是不
♪ Love is not ♪
爱不是...
♪ Love is not... ♪
爱
♪ Love. ♪
鲍比 我只是要告诉你.... 在我这么多年里
Bobby, I just have to tell you...  In all my years
我从没想过我会这么说
I never thought I'd say this
但是 黛博拉 梅辛 你往后稍稍
but, Debra Messing, it'll have to wait.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我只是真的爱你
I just really love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你喜欢爱情 兄弟？
You like love, bro?
哦 是的
Oh, yeah.
等等 什么...
Wait.  Wha...
哦
Oh.
哦 你是什么... ...  让我来做这个吧
Oh, what are you...  Just let me do this.
嗯...  嗯...
Uh...  Um...
哦 该死 我需要一枚戒指
Oh, shit. I need a ring.
呃 鲍伯 鲍伯... 塔玛拉 我可以借用你的戒指吗？
Uh, Bob Bobby...  Tamara, can I borrow your ring?
哦 好的  谢谢你
Oh, yeah.  Thank you.
鲍比 我...  亚伦 谢泼德
Bobby, I...  Aaron Shepard
我知道我们不是谈恋爱的人...
I know we're not relationship people...
...但是你能和我约会三个月吗？
...but will you date me for three months
然后我们再重新评估一下？
and then we'll reassess?
是的 鲍比 雷伯 我愿意和你约会三个月
Yes, Bobby Leiber, I will date you for three months
然后我们可以重新评估
and then we can reassess.
妈妈 发生了什么事？
Mommy, what's happening?
这是个奇迹
It's a miracle.
鲍比叔叔要和某人约会三个月
Uncle Bobby's gonna date someone for three months.
嘿 酷儿们！
Hey, queers!
我是博物馆这里的警卫
I'm the museum guard here.
只是要做一些除尘工作
Just gonna do some dusting.
你好 你为什么要给我除尘？
Hello. What are you doing dusting me?
我是女同性恋第一夫人埃莉诺 罗斯福
I'm lesbian first lady Eleanor Roosevelt.
嗨 我是塞斯 迈尔斯 扮演哈维 米尔克
Hi. I'm Seth Meyers as Harvey Milk.
你好
Hello.
我是凯南 汤普森 扮演詹姆斯 鲍德温
I'm Kenan Thompson as James Baldwin.
这是 "同性恋博物馆之夜"
It's a Night at the Gay Museum.
来这里吧
Come here.
每个人都是自由的
♪ Everybody's free ♪
感受美好
♪ To feel good ♪
每个人都是自由的
♪ Everybody's free ♪
耶
♪ Yeah ♪
感受美好
♪ To feel good ♪
兄弟姐妹
♪ Brother and sister ♪
我们会一起度过难关
♪ Together we'll make it through ♪
总有一天 灵魂将会带你
♪ Someday a spirit will lift you ♪
带你到那里
♪ And take you there ♪
每个人都是自由的
♪ Everybody's free ♪
感受美好
♪ To feel good. ♪
亚伦？ 妈妈
Aaron?  Mom.
呣
Mm.
鲍比  嗨
Bobby.  Hi.
啊 鲍比 这很壮观
Ah, Bobby, this is spectacular.
谢谢你  孩子们都很喜欢它
Thank you.  And the kids are loving it.
我很高兴你在这里 这对我来说意味着太多
I'm so glad you're here. It means so much to me
你能把它作为你旅行的一部分 对我来说意义重大
that you would make it part of your trip.
真的是这样  你是对的
It really does.  You were right.
他们当然应该看看这个
Of course they should see this.
这也是他们的历史
It's their history, too.
祝贺你
Congrats.
你在金赛量表上的等级为4
You're a four on the Kinsey Scale.
你是个双性恋
You're a bisexual.
好吧
Well.
再见！ 再见！
Bye!  Bye!
谢谢你教我关于利伯雷斯的事！
Thanks for teaching me about Liberace!
随时欢迎！
Anytime!
你知道 我们刚满三个月
You know, we just hit three months.
你觉得进展如何？
How do you think it's going?
我认为进展很好
I think it's going pretty well.
你认为情况如何？
How do you think it's going?
我觉得也很好
I think it's going pretty well, too.
哦 不错
Oh, good.
干得好  是啊
Good job.  Yeah.
再见 孩子们！ 再见 妈妈！
Bye, boys!  Bye, Mom!
你希望有一天能有孩子 对吗？
You want kids someday, right?
不   鲍比
No.  Bobby.
绝对不要  哦 鲍比
Absolutely not.  Oh, Bobby.
不！
No!
来吧 鲍比  不！不！
Come on. Bobby.  No! No!
你要去哪里？ 我不生孩子
Where are you going?  I'm not having children
无论我去哪里！ 哦 来吧！我想要孩子！
wherever I'm going!  Oh, come on! I want kids!
♪ God, I wish I would have known ♪
♪ When I was younger ♪
♪ That I should've just danced when I didn't want to ♪
♪ Hindsight's 20/20 ♪
♪ What's a boy to do ♪
♪ With a story in my head that's never true? ♪
♪ Hindsight's 20/20 ♪
♪ Mistakes, broken plates ♪
♪ Backseat third base ♪
♪ Cried in public yesterday ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Self care, truth or dare ♪
♪ Acting like I don't care ♪
♪ Screaming match, you were there ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Hindsight's 20/20 ♪
♪ God, I wish I would've known when I was younger ♪
♪ It's okay to smile when you're finally happy ♪
♪ Hindsight's 20/20 ♪
♪ Reach for their hands at the movie ♪
♪ Fall into someone ♪
♪ Let 'em have me ♪
♪ Yeah, hindsight's 20/20 ♪
♪ What's a boy to do ♪
♪ With a story in my head that's never true? ♪
♪ Hindsight's 20/20 ♪
♪ Mistakes, broken plates ♪
♪ Backseat third base ♪
♪ Cried in public yesterday ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Self care, truth or dare ♪
♪ Acting like I don't care ♪
♪ Screaming match, you were there ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Hindsight's 20/20 ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Hindsight's 20/20 ♪
♪ God, I wish I would've known when I was younger ♪
♪ That I should've just danced when I didn't want to. ♪